<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
  <publisher>The French Agency</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs</publisherurl>
  <lastBuildDate>2026-03-13 18:18</lastBuildDate>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Program Assistant]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 11 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-program-assistant-mesa-810.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=810&amp;role=Senior+Program+Assistant&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This recruitment will be used to fill two (2) vacancies in the Arts and Culture Department and (1) vacancy in the Human Resources Department . This recruitment will also be used to create a Citywide list to fill possible future vacancies in all assignment areas. &nbsp; &nbsp; A Senior Program Assistant is a paraprofessional class that performs a variety of assignments involving public contact work of a specialized nature.&nbsp; Employees in this class are responsible for administering, monitoring, and/or implementing a major program, process, or technical functional area within a unit or department. &nbsp;In addition, incumbents must possess advanced technical knowledge in specific functional areas; have the ability to explain and interpret information; work independently without specific instruction; and regularly exercise independent judgment when making decisions regarding the disposition of matters related to the program areas. &nbsp;Duties may include supervising clerical and/or paraprofessional staff, working with accounting or financial data, and relieving supervisors of administrative details. &nbsp;This class performs related duties as required. This class is distinguished from the Program Assistant class by the more advanced technical and complex nature of the work performed; independent discretion in regards to a program, process, or technical functional area; and supervisory responsibilities (by assignment) . &nbsp;Minimal supervision is received from an administrative or professional staff person, unit director, or department manager. &nbsp;Employees in this class may be required to work evenings, weekends, and holidays for special events&nbsp; (by assignment) . &nbsp;When part-time or Grant-Funded this classification has been designated as a non-classified, non-merit system, at-will position. &nbsp;This class is FLSA nonexempt. Please refer to the link below for the full job description and additional information regarding assignments, preferred qualif]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Police Grants Specialist]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 03 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/police-grants-specialist-mesa-832.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=832&amp;role=Police+Grants+Specialist&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[A Police Grants Specialist is responsible for generating, monitoring, and analyzing financial reports and documents, in addition to grants coordination and management. &nbsp;Duties include: &nbsp;overseeing the financial tracking, reconciling, and reporting of multiple state and federal grants and task forces; monitoring revenue and expenditures, ensuring compliance with contractual and other program obligations while utilizing appropriate accounting procedures and adhering to reporting and audit deadlines; assisting with budget related tasks while coordinating with City Financial Services and with the different divisions within the Police Department; analyzing and summarizing financial budget/actual reports achieving a concise, user-friendly format; and other special projects such as reconciling overtime and expenses for special events, overseeing internally and externally restricted police funds, monitoring and summarizing expenditures of various Police Department programs, invoicing intergovernmental organizations and third-party vendors for police services rendered, and maintaining detailed records of monetary and non-monetary donations received. &nbsp;The Police Grants Specialist may supervise paraprofessional and/or clerical staff. &nbsp;This class performs related duties as required. This class is distinguished from the Financial Specialist class by the more technical work performed and overall oversight with respect to grants management, as well as the additional financial tracking projects and budget work. &nbsp;The Police Grants Specialist is supervised by the Financial Coordinator. &nbsp;This class is FLSA exempt-administrative. Please refer to the link below for the full job description and additional information regarding assignments, preferred qualifications, and essential functions.&nbsp;]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recreation Assistant (Part-time, Temporary, Non-benefited)]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 12 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/recreation-assistant-part-time-temporary-non-benefited-chandler-867.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=867&amp;role=Recreation+Assistant+(Part-time,+Temporary,+Non-benefited)&amp;company=City+of+Chandler</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Chandler]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Chandler Community Services Department is currently seeking qualified individuals interested in joining our team as a&nbsp; Recreation Assistant (part-time, temporary, non-benefited). This position serves at the discretion of the department director. The position is scheduled to work Tuesday and Thursday from 4:00–8:00 p.m., and Friday–Sunday from 1:00–5:00 p.m. on a rotating basis. Current City of Chandler employees may only hold one position and are not eligible for additional part-time or secondary positions within the City of Chandler. Why work for Chandler? • Open and collaborative environment &nbsp; • Dress code is business casual, with jeans on Fridays • Accrue 1 hour of paid Statutory Sick Leave (SSL) for every 30 hours worked, eligible for use immediately following accrual; may use up to 40 hours of SSL per tax calendar year • Free Tumbleweed Recreation Center membership • Flexible schedule Who we are Community Services The Community Services Department enhances the quality of life in Chandler through a vast provision of diverse and affordable educational and recreational experiences. We create community through people, parks, and programs. From connecting people to lifelong learning through community libraries to providing at least one Neighborhood Park per square mile of residential development to make play accessible for all ages. Our employees drive every decision, every innovation, and every aspect of our department culture to make Chandler a premier community. &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Recreation The Recreation Division champions everyday experiences that encourage the community to discover, imagine, and grow. The cornerstone of every neighborhood, our innovative events, programs, and services strengthen community vitality and foster healthy, enriched lifestyles. Our employees play today for a better tomorrow. Who we are looking for We are looking for energetic, team-oriented individuals with a passion for exceptional customer service. As a key ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>General</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lifeguard I/II (part-time, temporary, non-benefited)]]></title>
    <date>Mon, 05 Ja</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/lifeguard-iii-part-time-temporary-non-benefited-chandler-877.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=877&amp;role=Lifeguard+I/II+(part-time,+temporary,+non-benefited)&amp;company=City+of+Chandler</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Chandler]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Chandler Community Services Department is currently seeking qualified individuals interested in joining our team as a Lifeguard I or Lifeguard II (part-time, temporary, non-benefited). This position serves at the discretion of the department director. &nbsp; Current City of Chandler employees may only hold one position and are not eligible for additional part-time or secondary positions within the City of Chandler. Why work for Chandler? • Open and collaborative environment &nbsp; • Dress code is business casual, with jeans on Fridays • Accrue 1 hour of paid Statutory Sick Leave (SSL) for every 30 hours worked, eligible for use immediately following accrual; may use up to 40 hours of SSL per tax calendar year • Free Tumbleweed Recreation Center membership • Flexible schedule Who we are Community Services The Community Services Department enhances the quality of life in Chandler through a vast provision of diverse and affordable educational and recreational experiences. We create community through people, parks, and programs. From connecting people to lifelong learning through community libraries to providing at least one Neighborhood Park per square mile of residential development to make play accessible for all ages. Our employees drive every decision, every innovation, and every aspect of our department culture to make Chandler a premier community. &nbsp; Recreation The Recreation Division champions everyday experiences that encourage the community to discover, imagine, and grow. The cornerstone of every neighborhood, our innovative events, programs, and services strengthen community vitality and foster healthy, enriched lifestyles. Our employees play today for a better tomorrow. Who we are looking for Chandler Aquatics is seeking responsible, self-motivated, and energetic Lifeguards to join our team. We are looking for someone with the knowledge and skills to recognize and respond to aquatic emergencies, along with the knowledge and skill set to instr]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>General</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Accountant]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 11 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-accountant-scottsdale-884.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=884&amp;role=Senior+Accountant&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Join our team and be a part of Scottsdale’s future! We are looking for an enthusiastic team player who is looking to make an impact through their work. Our office is in the heart of Old Town, across from city hall. This position performs complex accounting work in all areas of financial reporting. This position will annually receive 12 paid holidays, 96 hours of medical leave, 3 weeks of vacation, and health and dental benefits start immediately. Productivity, performance, and job satisfaction are encouraged through a balanced workload, schedule flexibility, and a commitment to professional development. Apply today if you are interested in joining our high-performing team dedicated to serving a world-class community. Please note: The department asks that you attach a Cover Letter and Resume to your application. Anticipated starting salary may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity. The midpoint salary is $103,750.40 annually. &nbsp; The City of Scottsdale offers: 12 Paid Holidays, which includes 1 Floating Holiday Vacation Accrual; starts at 10.3 hours/month, eligible for use immediately following accrual Sick Leave Accrual; 8 hours/month, eligible for use immediately following accrual&nbsp; Medical (which includes behavioral health coverage), Dental and Vision benefits effective first day of employment City Paid Basic Life Insurance (equal to one times employee annual salary); option of Supplemental Life Insurance Tuition Reimbursement; $2,500/year Participation in the Arizona State Retirement System (ASRS) Defined benefit plan with mandatory employer and employee contributions currently at 12% which includes a Long-Term Disability benefit Supplemental Retirement Plans through Nationwide; 457&nbsp; Pet Insurance Bilingual pay compensation Robust Employee Wellness plan with flexible incentives Access to several city-owned fitness and recreational facilities at no cost Please visit the&nbsp; Human Resources and Benefits Information]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ADMINISTRATIVE SPECIALIST (Police)]]></title>
    <date>Fri, 13 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/administrative-specialist-police-surprise-901.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=901&amp;role=ADMINISTRATIVE+SPECIALIST+(Police)&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[**Interviews for this position will be scheduled for March 31, 2026** &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Applications will be reviewed after the posting closes, and qualified candidates will be contacted once the screening process is complete. SUMMARY Incumbents are responsible for performing confidential data entry, preparing reports, preparing and proofing original correspondence, performing basic accounting functions for assigned area, and conducting moderately complex research. EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE Associates Degree, and one year of progressively responsible clerical experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience sufficient to successfully perform the essential duties of the job such as those listed in the job description. &nbsp;Additional education cannot be substituted for experience. CERTIFICATIONS, LICENSES, REGISTRATIONS None SELECTION PROCESS Applicants whose education, training and experience most closely meet the needs of the position may be invited to participate in a selection process to include panel interviews. Successful candidates will receive a post-offer, pre-employment background screening to include: Fingerprinting Criminal Background screening Education and Experience Verification Polygraph Examination Drug Screen&nbsp; E-Verify To view the full job description, including work environment and physical demands, click HERE The City of Surprise is an EEO/ADA reasonable accommodation employer &nbsp;]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[PAYROLL SPECIALIST]]></title>
    <date>Mon, 09 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/payroll-specialist-surprise-908.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=908&amp;role=PAYROLL+SPECIALIST&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[We’re looking for an experienced and talented Payroll Specialist to join our dynamic and inclusive team! You will be responsible for payroll processing and ensuring accurate and timely payment to our employees. To be successful, you will have at least two years of full-cycle payroll processing experience and a thorough understanding of payroll tax regulations. A successful candidate will have the opportunity to demonstrate their attention to detail and will possess strong organizational, communication and problem-solving skills. If you have a passion for payroll and want to be part of an organization that values each employee and their contributions, then we want to hear from you! SUMMARY Incumbents are engaged in daily payroll functions and process citywide biweekly payroll and work with highly sensitive, confidential personnel information. Responsibilities include applying applicable employee policy and mandated legislative regulations, data entry and maintenance of databases and logs, processing vendor/agency interface payments, termination pay, retroactive pay and deductions, preparing quarterly and annual reports, assisting in the development and training of work procedures, providing customer assistance, and insuring internal/external deadlines are met. EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE &nbsp; High School Diploma or G.E.D. and two years full-cycle payroll processing experience; additional education cannot be substituted for experience. CERTIFICATIONS, LICENSES, REGISTRATIONS&nbsp; None SELECTION PROCESS Applicants whose education, training and experience most closely meet the needs of the position may be invited to participate in a selection process to include a panel interview. Successful candidates will receive a post-offer, pre-employment background screening to include: Fingerprinting Criminal Background screening E-Verify Education and Experience Verification To view the full job description, including work environment and physical demands, click HERE The City ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Administration</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[BUSINESS MANAGER- FINANCIAL]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/business-manager-financial-surprise-915.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=915&amp;role=BUSINESS+MANAGER-+FINANCIAL&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Surprise is a fast-growing community where strong financial leadership is essential to turning plans into reality. As a Business Manager - Financial, you’ll play a central role in developing and managing department budgets, analyzing complex financial data, and supporting oversight of the development agreements and contracts that shape the City’s future. This role is ideal for someone with strong skills in Excel for purposes of reconciling data from multiple sources and translating complex financial information into clear deliverables. You’ll work in a collaborative, solutions-oriented environment where finance is a strategic partner. If you enjoy digging into details, improving processes, and using your technical skills to support responsible growth and high-quality public services, the City of Surprise offers the opportunity to make a visible and lasting impact. SUMMARY Incumbents are responsible for supervising staff, oversight and managing functions within their assigned areas with supervision from the Assistant Director. When assigned as the Business Manager - Financial, this includes completing and monitoring all financial transactions and Development Agreements; participating in department audits; preparing, monitoring, and analyzing Department budgets; analyzing operations of the various Department programs; managing grants, contracts and IGA’s; and preparing financial and budget impact analysis and statements regarding possible program and operational changes within the Department.&nbsp; EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE &nbsp; Bachelor’s Degree in a related field and five years of technical experience, including three years of supervisory or lead experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience sufficient to successfully perform the essential duties of the job such as those listed above. &nbsp;Additional education cannot be substituted for experience. CERTIFICATIONS, LICENSES, REGISTRATIONS &nbsp; None SELECTION PROCESS Applicants]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[CITY AUDITOR]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/city-auditor-surprise-916.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=916&amp;role=CITY+AUDITOR&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[WE ARE SEEKING Our ideal candidate is a&nbsp;principled audit leader&nbsp;with deep expertise in municipal finance and&nbsp;Yellow Book (GAGAS) standards. They possess a sophisticated understanding of complex audit controls and a proven track record in both financial and operational analysis. As a&nbsp;strategic communicator, they bring an extensive professional reporting background necessary to drive public transparency and provide clear, actionable insights to City leadership. ABOUT THE CITY AUDITOR The City Auditor is a City Council appointed position, responsible for conducting independent appraisals and strategic evaluation as part of the city’s audit program and annual audit plan, providing a clear and unbiased line of communication to the Mayor and City Council. &nbsp;The City Auditor will bring transparency, objectivity, and accountability in financial, performance, and attestation engagements covering internal controls and compliance. &nbsp; &nbsp; To provide for the independence of the city audit program, the city auditor will be an appointed official functionally reporting to the audit committee. &nbsp;The City Auditor leads a professional staff which includes a Senior Internal Auditor and Internal Auditor. City Auditor's Mission Statement:&nbsp; To provide independent, objective, accurate and timely auditing services that are designed to improve operations, cultivate transparency and accountability. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES The duties listed below are intended only as general illustrations of the various types of work that may be performed. Specific statements of duties not included do not exclude them from the position if the work is similar, related, or a logical assignment to the position.&nbsp; Appoints, supervises, directs, disciplines, and terminates employees under the supervision of the city auditor Complies will all city policies and procedures of the city unless inconsistent with Municipal Code Develops a flexible, risk-based inter]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business License Coordinator]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 12 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/business-license-coordinator-apache-junction-954.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=954&amp;role=Business+License+Coordinator&amp;company=City+of+Apache+Junction</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Apache Junction]]></company>
    <city>Apache Junction</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[(Anticipated Hiring Range: $23.85 - $25.06/hour) Positions assigned to this class perform duties related to the issuance, renewal and auditing of city business licenses, vendor applications, peddler permits and permits for other special events.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>General</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Comptroller - Finance (0326)]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 10 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/comptroller-finance-0326-flagstaff-986.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=986&amp;role=Comptroller+-+Finance+(0326)&amp;company=Coconino+County</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Coconino County]]></company>
    <city>Flagstaff</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Under general direction performs professional accounting, administrative and analytical work of considerable difficulty in the management of the County's official accounting records; manages and oversees the creation of the County’s financial statements and various audits, including the County’s annual financial audit, performs other related work as assigned.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Assistant Director - Finance (0326)]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/assistant-director-finance-0326-flagstaff-991.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=991&amp;role=Assistant+Director+-+Finance+(0326)&amp;company=Coconino+County</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Coconino County]]></company>
    <city>Flagstaff</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Under general direction performs professional accounting, administrative and analytical work of considerable difficulty in the management of the County's official accounting records; perform other related work as assigned.&nbsp;]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Consultant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-12</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-consultant-phoenix-1254.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1254&amp;role=Accounting+Consultant&amp;company=Massena+Business+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Massena Business Services]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Company Description

Our Company assists with almost everything on the backside of the business, however it is primarily accounting, payroll and HR work. We will do software RFI/RFP/implementations, process improvements/writing SOPs, inventory control, annual reporting, setting up new entities, recruiting and soon our expansion of group events at our new property in the White Mountains. Our goal is to help our clients be successful and give them the peace of mind they need to sleep at night. We keep our ears open for pain points and jump in with some possible solutions to help. Referrals built our company, we do not advertise yet and we want to continue to grow due to our excellent reputation.

Role Description

The Accounting Consultant is a business partner to our clients. This position has flexible hours. It is Part-time to start and could move to Full-time if you like. It is mostly remote in the state of Arizona. Occasionally we need to go to a client to get them set up for remote work or if there is some sort of issue we cannot manage through screen-sharing, which is pretty rare. If you have excellent customer service, attention to detail, organizational and problem-solving skills, strong general ledger and cash/accrual accounting knowledge as well as a good understanding of how a business runs you should do very well in this position.

Essential Function

Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.
• Set up new chart of accounts or clean up an existing one.
• Set up item codes and map them in QuickBooks.
• Build custom reports in QBO when necessary
• Process sales tax returns
• Reconcile/adjust Inventory
• Monthly audit of client financial records for accuracy from bookkeepers. Address any issues with bookkeepers and keep your manager informed of repeat or large errors/issues.
• Asset and Liability account reconciliations
• Do monthly close on all assigned clients and pull financial reports ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Construction Accountant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-13</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-construction-accountant-phoenix-1255.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1255&amp;role=Senior+Construction+Accountant&amp;company=Ganem+Construction+LLC</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Ganem Construction LLC]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Ganem ConstructionSenior Construction Accountant

Location: Phoenix, AZ

Position Overview

Ganem Companies is seeking a Senior Construction Accountant to join our growing team in Phoenix. This role is ideal for an experienced accounting professional with a strong background in construction accounting, multi-entity financial management, and Sage 300 (Timberline).

The Senior Construction Accountant will play a key role in managing the full accounting cycle for multiple entities within an $80-$100M annual construction organization operating across multiple states. This individual will work closely with leadership and report to senior finance leadership, with the opportunity to grow into Controller or Assistant Controller responsibilities.

We are looking for someone who thrives in a fast-paced construction environment, understands job cost accounting, and can maintain accuracy across multiple entities and projects.

Key Responsibilities
• Manage the full accounting cycle including general ledger, journal entries, reconciliations, and month-end close.
• Maintain accurate financial records across multiple entities and states.
• Perform construction job cost accounting and ensure proper cost allocation and project financial tracking.
• Prepare and review monthly financial statements and supporting schedules.
• Reconcile bank accounts, credit cards, and balance sheet accounts.
• Assist with budgeting, forecasting, and variance analysis.
• Work closely with project management teams to ensure accurate project financial reporting and job cost tracking.
• Support year-end audit preparation and tax reporting.
• Maintain and improve accounting processes and internal controls.
• Assist leadership with financial reporting and analysis related to company performance.

Required Qualifications
• Minimum 5 years of accounting experience in the construction industry
• Strong understanding of construction accounting and job costing
• Experience with Sage 300 / Timberline
• Experience ]]></description>
    <salary>90000-110000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Alternative Investment Accountant 2]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-12</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/alternative-investment-accountant-2-tempe-1256.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1256&amp;role=Alternative+Investment+Accountant+2&amp;company=U.S.+Bank+National+Association</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[U.S. Bank National Association]]></company>
    <city>Tempe</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[At U.S. Bank, we’re on a journey to do our best. Helping the customers and businesses we serve to make better and smarter financial decisions and enabling the communities we support to grow and succeed. We believe it takes all of us to bring our shared ambition to life, and each person is unique in their potential. A career with U.S. Bank gives you a wide, ever-growing range of opportunities to discover what makes you thrive at every stage of your career. Try new things, learn new skills and discover what you excel at—all from Day One.

Job Description

Alternative Investments Associates and Accountants work as part of a team responsible for providing accounting, administration and investor servicing for hedge funds, private equity funds and closed-end registered products. Individuals calculate net asset value(s) and disseminate financial and performance information to the investment advisor and their investors. Acting as primary fund accountant on multiple relationships, ensures all fund accounting functions are in completed in accordance with Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP). Records trade information, income/expense activity and applies valuation of securities in the portfolio accounting system. Enters and reconciles all investor contributions and withdrawals in the partnership accounting system. Allocates fund level profits to individual investors for preparation and distribution of investor statements. Reviews and coordinates fund expense analysis and expense processing. Prepares fund financial statements, audit and tax schedules.

Basic Qualifications
• Bachelor's degree in Accounting, Finance or a business-related field, or equivalent work experience
• Two to five years of related experience, preferably in portfolio/partnership accounting

Preferred Skills/Experience
• Thorough knowledge in accounting, reporting, and analysis
• Ability to identify and resolve/escalate complex problems with minimal guidance
• Ability to manage multiple tasks/pro]]></description>
    <salary>66640-78400</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Staff Accountant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-12</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/sr-staff-accountant-phoenix-1257.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1257&amp;role=Sr.+Staff+Accountant&amp;company=Red+Seal+Recruiting</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Red Seal Recruiting]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Join this Dynamic Corporate Accounting Team as Sr. Staff Accountant!

Are you ready to play a pivotal role in shaping the financial future of a growing company? We’re seeking a motivated Sr. Staff Accountant to join this innovative team and help drive financial excellence to new heights.

Key Responsibilities
• Oversee and maintain the company’s accounts receivable ledger with precision
• Create and distribute invoices while following up with clients to ensure prompt payment
• Resolve billing discrepancies diplomatically and efficiently
• Work effectively with sales team
• Work with purchase orders and expense reports and ensure accuracy
• Sales and Use Tax compliance
• Perform account reconciliations between AP, AR and general ledger
• Support month-end closing procedures and additional accounting functions as needed

Qualifications
• Bachelor’s degree in accounting or finance
• Minimum 3 years of AR, AP, GL experience
• ERP accounting system experience a must
• Sales and Use Tax experience a plus
• Exceptional attention to detail and commitment to accuracy
• Strong communication skills with a customer-focused approach
• Ability to prioritize effectively and meet deadlines independently
• Advanced proficiency in Microsoft Excel
• Solid understanding of GAAP and fundamental accounting principles
• Availability to work in the Phoenix office Monday through Friday]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Tax Senior Manager, Customs and International Trade]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-12</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/tax-senior-manager-customs-and-international-trade-phoenix-1258.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1258&amp;role=Tax+Senior+Manager,+Customs+and+International+Trade&amp;company=BDO+USA</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[BDO USA]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Summary

JOB DESCRIPTION

A Tax Senior Manager, Customs and International Trade is responsible for advising clients on and identifying potential trade issues and opportunities providing advice to clients, in a variety of industries, on import and export matters. In this role, the Customs and International Trade Senior Manager will be charged with marketing, networking and business development within his/her area of experience and specialization and recognizing potential changes in tax policy and applying new policies pertaining to customs and international trade matters.

Job Duties
• Technical Duties:
• Assists clients and BDO client service teams in developing ideas, structures and transactions with a focus on customs and international trade matters – to optimize the tax position for clients
• Researches, writes, and reviews international trade advice in areas relating to the Harmonized Tariff Schedule, customs federal regulations, NAFTA, entry processes, and customs valuation
• Researches U.S. and international import and export trade matters
• Identifies need for other expert resources, internal and external, to assist when necessary to introduce opportunities for tax savings for clients and prospective clients
• Understands, develops and maintains workplans for tax consulting projects
• Assists with the implementation of Firm tax strategies
• Formulates ideas and deliver possible trade savings opportunities
• Works with other Firm specialists and client service teams on client and proposal work
• Organizes and conducts effective internal CPE training sessions in the area of specialization
• Establishes relationship with BDO customs experts in jurisdictions throughout BDO International
• Identifies opportunities for and assists in drafting tax alerts in international customs and global trade tax matters
• Assists in managing client expectations
• Other duties as required

Supervisory Responsibilities
• Supervises the day-to-day workload of Customs and Intern]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Tax Senior Manager, Credits & Incentives]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-12</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/tax-senior-manager-credits-amp-incentives-phoenix-1259.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1259&amp;role=Tax+Senior+Manager,+Credits+&amp;+Incentives&amp;company=Bakertilly</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Bakertilly]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Overview

Baker Tilly is a leading advisory, tax and assurance firm, providing clients with a genuine coast-to-coast and global advantage in major regions of the U.S. and in many of the world's leading financial centers - New York, London, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Chicago and Boston. Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP and Baker Tilly US, LLP (Baker Tilly) provide professional services through an alternative practice structure in accordance with the AICPA Code of Professional Conduct and applicable laws, regulations and professional standards. Baker Tilly US, LLP is a licensed independent CPA firm that provides attest services to its clients. Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP and its subsidiary entities provide tax and business advisory services to their clients. Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP and its subsidiary entities are not licensed CPA firms.

Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP and Baker Tilly US, LLP, trading as Baker Tilly, are independent members of Baker Tilly International, a worldwide network of independent accounting and business advisory firms in 141 territories, with 43,000 professionals and a combined worldwide revenue of $5.2 billion. Visitbakertilly.comor join the conversation onLinkedIn,FacebookandInstagram.

Please discuss the work location status with your Baker Tilly talent acquisition professional to understand the requirements for an opportunity you are exploring.

Baker Tilly is an equal opportunity/affirmative action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability or protected veteran status, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other legally protected basis, in accordance with applicable federal, state or local law.

Any unsolicited resumes submitted through our website or to Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP, employee e-mail accounts are considered property of Baker Tilly Advisory Group, LP, and are not subject to payment of agency fees. In o]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Tax Associate]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-13</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-tax-associate-scottsdale-1260.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=1260&amp;role=Senior+Tax+Associate&amp;company=Kforce+Inc</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Kforce Inc]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Responsibilities

Kforce's client, a publicly traded growing company is seeking a Senior Tax Associate This role can sit in Scottsdale, Arizona, or Princeton, NJ. The role will be 3 days in the office and 2 days remote. They will be responsible for supporting the Senior Manager for all tax planning activities, including US federal and state income tax, transaction tax return support, cash tax optimization, credits and incentives, and transaction diligence. Responsibilities include:
• Calculate tax basis, 704(b) capital accounts, and transaction-related impacts while explaining the impacts for tax compliance
• Preparation of memos and presentations to document diligence and transactions
• Review of financial models, including cash taxes, partnership capital accounts, and credit and incentives related items
• Assist with tax research for unique tax fact patterns
• Collaborate closely with Accounting, Business Development, and Portfolio Finance to support transactions and ensure tax modeling accuracy
• Drive process-change to optimize tax planning and enhance efficiency

Requirements
• Bachelor's degree in Accounting, Finance, Business, Education, Taxation, Business/Administration, or similar
• 3+ years of federal and state tax planning or compliance for partnerships with a public accounting firm or large corporate tax department; Experience with private equity or real estate tax is a plus
• Partnership (Sub K) tax experience is a must
• Experience drafting memos and presentations
• Desire to learn data translation using Power BI, Alteryx, and Excel
• Demonstrated ability to work cross-functionally and explain tax-related items to non-tax audiences
• Strong analytical and Excel modeling skills, with proficiency in PowerPoint
• Private equity or real estate tax is plus
• Industry experience in energy, private equity, or real estate is a plus

The pay range is the lowest to highest compensation we reasonably in good faith believe we would pay at posting for this role. We]]></description>
    <salary>100000-116000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Utilities Systems Analyst I/II - SCADA]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 11 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/utilities-systems-analyst-iii-scada-mesa-811.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=811&amp;role=Utilities+Systems+Analyst+I/II+-+SCADA&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; This recruitment will be used to fill two (2) vacancies at either the Utilities Systems Analyst I or Utilities Systems Analyst I I level. First review of applications will be on Tuesday, February 17, 2026, and weekly thereafter as needed. Utilities Systems Analyst I ($81,814.93 - $118,687.71) A Utilities Systems Analyst I provides technical support for the Utilities Department Supervisory Control and Data Acquisition (SCADA) system. &nbsp;The incumbent’s duties include programming, modifying, and testing graphic interfaces for use by the Water Treatment Plant Operators as well as creating and running reports. &nbsp;Other duties include: &nbsp;utilizing advanced graphics and programming concepts, tools, and technologies such as Visual Basic and 3D graphics animation to develop Operator control interfaces; utilizing Programmable Logic Controller (PLC) programming languages such as Ladder, Function Block, Structured Text, and Sequential Function Chart logic to develop control programs; installing, configuring, and maintaining workstations, laptops, and other peripherals both stand alone and connected to the Utilities network; assisting in evaluating hardware, software, and peripherals for new and existing facilities; testing and modifying new and existing applications used for operational interfacing with PLC’s; verifying Process and Instrumentation (P&amp;ID) and electrical drawings for accuracy, and verifying that drawings agree with control descriptions and plant specifications; creating SCADA Human Machine Interface (HMI) graphics and associated database; developing and implementing SCADA alarm functions; troubleshooting the system and correcting problems; developing daily, weekly, monthly, and yearly reports as required by management and plant personnel; and developing SCADA documentation and performing related duties as required. Incumbents are required to carry out assignments without detailed instruction or guidance. &nbsp;The Utilities Systems Analyst I]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Police Aviation Administrator (Aviation Unit Manager)]]></title>
    <date>Sun, 08 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/police-aviation-administrator-aviation-unit-manager-mesa-818.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=818&amp;role=Police+Aviation+Administrator+(Aviation+Unit+Manager)&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[First review of applications will be Monday, March 16, 2026.&nbsp; This classification has been designated as a non-classified, non-merit system, at-will position . A Police Aviation Administrator is a civilian position responsible for managing the activities of personnel assigned to the Aviation Section of the Police Department. &nbsp;Duties include: &nbsp;evaluating pilots, observers, and mechanics in the performance of their duties; reviewing mission logs, operation reports, and completed departmental incident and supplemental reports; preparing deployment schedules for crew members and aircraft; ensuring section members comply with Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), Department, and Aviation Section regulations and procedures pertaining to Aviation Section Functions; identifying potential problems and taking appropriate action to correct and prevent recurrences; and coordinating and facilitating required training. &nbsp;Additional duties include: &nbsp;preparing and evaluating the section budget; coordinating with procurement personnel; reviewing and executing various contracts; writing and executing grants; working on strategic initiatives; making recommendations on aircraft replacement; overseeing, coordinating, and working with the pilot training vendor in the standardizing of initial pilot training across all phases of flight and ground training; maintaining all training documentation including qualification requirements; maintaining all appropriate flight manuals; assuring compliance with Departmental and FAA rules and regulations concerning the qualifications and training of pilots and observers; maintaining current copies of the FAA pilot certificates, ratings, and medical certificates held by each pilot; maintaining current documentation/records on audiograms of Section Personnel approved for hearing tests under the requirements of the hearing Conservation Plan under AVI 42; schedule/conduct training for upgrading airman certificates; conducting train]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Court Specialist]]></title>
    <date>Sun, 08 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/court-specialist-mesa-819.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=819&amp;role=Court+Specialist&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[There are current vacancies in the Customer Relations Unit and Court Operations Unit; this recruitment will also be used to create an eligible list for future vacancies. &nbsp;If assigned to Court Operations, you will be required to work Fridays/Weekends and Holidays on a rotating basis.&nbsp; If assigned to Court Operations, because of access to the Mesa Police Department and the confidential, sensitive nature of information handled, successful completion of a background investigation is required.&nbsp; A Court Specialist performs a variety of responsible, highly skilled clerical and paraprofessional tasks including administrative, judicial support, and public contact duties in one of the operational divisions within the Municipal Court. &nbsp;Assignments require a high degree of thoroughness and accuracy in performing administrative details within established time constraints while complying with strict Court policies and procedures. &nbsp;The Court Specialist position is responsible for performing related duties as required. Customer Relations Unit Assignment: &nbsp; Provides customer service to court visitors in person and on the phone. &nbsp;Manages and reconciles a cash drawer daily. &nbsp;Conducts civil traffic Arraignments for uncontested civil traffic and parking violations at the customer service counter according to Administrative Order 2014-102. &nbsp;Reconciles the daily financial report by verifying amounts to be refunded or transferred. &nbsp;Reviews financial and other computer transactions and electronic documentation on a case to ensure that computer records correspond and when errors are identified, routes the issue accordingly. &nbsp;Reviews reports for driver’s license suspensions, traffic school completions, fines paid in full, and restitution disbursement to victims. &nbsp;Processes and provides certified copy requests within legally required timelines. &nbsp;Successful applicants will be required to train and cover in all areas of Customer Re]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Police Projects Portfolio Manager]]></title>
    <date>Fri, 06 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/police-projects-portfolio-manager-mesa-820.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=820&amp;role=Police+Projects+Portfolio+Manager&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[A Police Projects Portfolio Manager is responsible for planning, coordinating, and managing a portfolio of strategic initiatives and projects that support the operational and long-term goals of the Mesa Police Department. &nbsp;This position provides leadership on project execution directly over assigned projects and indirectly over strategic initiatives assigned to command staff. &nbsp;The Police Projects Portfolio Manager is also responsible for performing a variety of advanced, professional-level work in planning, coordinating, and managing one or more large-scale, highly complex/high risk projects, which may impact multiple agencies, citizens, or multiple units, sections, or departments through the project’s lifecycle and implementation. &nbsp;Duties include: &nbsp;developing, implementing, and training staff on project management standards, strategic planning, and related activities; managing projects using the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK); ensuring accuracy, timeliness, and completeness of all project processes and documentation, management reports, and project status reporting according to PMBOK; organizing, planning, and directing all project activities throughout the project’s lifecycle and implementation (example: &nbsp;research/analysis, requirements gathering, risk assessments, technical alternatives, development, and implementation planning); acting as primary contact for each project; developing project proposals which include business justification, return-on-investment, risk assessment, and goals/objectives; facilitating meetings with customers, staff, vendors, and contractors in support of project activities; facilitating resolution of project issues; scheduling and tracking resource needs and activities (including City staff, contractors, and outside agencies) to meet project objectives, and ensure overall quality of work; ensuring all work is done in alignment with City and PD’s long-term strategies; managing formal solicitations a]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Parks, Recreation and Community Facilities Department Director]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/parks-recreation-and-community-facilities-department-director-mesa-822.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=822&amp;role=Parks,+Recreation+and+Community+Facilities+Department+Director&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Mesa is seeking a visionary executive to serve as its next Parks, Recreation &amp; Community Facilities Director. This nationally accredited system blends neighborhood parks, recreation programming, aquatics, and major public venues into one of the most visible and community-impacting departments in the region. Serving more than 3 million annual visits, the department includes hundreds of parks and basins, sports complexes, recreation centers, adaptive and youth programs, aquatics facilities, a convention center, amphitheater, event venues, and professional spring training stadiums.&nbsp; The Director provides strategic and operational leadership to 351 full-time employees and oversees a $53 million operating budget, balancing community access with financial sustainability. This role serves as the City’s primary authority on parks and recreation, advising executive leadership and City Council while ensuring high-quality service delivery across a diverse system. This classification has been designated as a non-classified, non-merit system, at-will position. The ideal candidate will be: Strategic and Operational: Able to see the big picture while understanding the realities of delivering programs and maintaining facilities every day.&nbsp; A Strong People Leade r:&nbsp;This department spans long-tenured professionals, seasonal and part-time staff, and young employees just entering the workforce. The Director must build trust, develop leaders, and foster a culture of accountability and inclusion. Comfortable in Public and Political Environments:&nbsp; You will represent the department with City leadership, advisory boards, regional partners, and the community. Diplomacy, clarity, and credibility are essential.&nbsp; Financially Savvy: The role involves oversight of a large and diverse operating budget, balancing general fund responsibilities with cost recovery expectations in commercial and program areas. Collaborative Across the Organization:&nbsp; Success]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Museum Exhibitions Coordinator]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 04 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/museum-exhibitions-coordinator-mesa-824.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=824&amp;role=Museum+Exhibitions+Coordinator&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[First review of applications will be on Monday, February 23rd, 2026. A Museum Exhibitions Coordinator is responsible for developing strategy, management, design, construction, installation, and maintenance of permanent galleries and temporary museum exhibitions; establishing priorities for the unit within the context of the entire museum; implementing planning and evaluation for each exhibition in cooperation with other museum management staff; producing exhibit related deliverables such as scaled floor plans, elevations, models, and other documents; developing, coordinating, and monitoring the unit budget; coordinating procurement of supplies and tools; obtaining building, fire, and other permits as necessary, and meeting all code requirements regarding exhibitions; and performing the design fabrication/construction, installation, and repair of interpretive and educational exhibits.&nbsp; This classification may supervise the Museum Exhibits Preparator and/or the Museum Exhibits Technician classifications, as well as temporary agency personnel and volunteers.&nbsp; This class performs related duties as required.&nbsp; This class is distinguished from the curator staff by the absence of responsibilities for acquisition or care of collections.&nbsp; This class is supervised by a Museum Administrator or Museum Curator.&nbsp; This class is FLSA exempt-professional. Please refer to the link below for the full job description and additional information regarding assignments, preferred qualifications, and essential functions.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Utilities Control Center Operator]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 03 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/utilities-control-center-operator-mesa-829.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=829&amp;role=Utilities+Control+Center+Operator&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[First review of applications will be on Monday, March 9, 2026, then weekly thereafter until filled. A Utilities Control Center Operator, under direct supervision, is responsible for learning how to monitor and operate the Supervisory Control and Data Acquisition (SCADA) system in the recording and regulating of water distribution and the monitoring and recording of natural gas usage and wastewater flow.&nbsp; Additionally, incumbents will be responsible for receiving after-hours calls from City of Mesa customers, responding to their inquiries, and dispatching appropriate personnel as required.&nbsp; When handling calls, an employee must make determinations and decisions regarding the urgency of the problem, the appropriate City department to handle the problem, and stand-by-duty personnel to be contacted.&nbsp; This class performs related duties as required. Employees in this class may be required to work varying shifts, weekends, and holidays.&nbsp; This class is distinguished from the Utilities Distribution Controller class by its status as a trainee class in which incumbents learn the duties of a Utilities Distribution Controller.&nbsp; The Utilities Control Center Operator receives close-to-general supervision from the Utilities Control Center Supervisor and/or the Utilities Distribution Shift Leader, who review the employee's work through work in progress, meetings, and by the evaluation of results achieved.&nbsp; Employees in this class will be eligible to progress after one year of service by noncompetitive promotion to the classification of Utilities Distribution Controller.&nbsp; Promotion is accomplished after successful completion of on-the-job training, achievement of successful performance evaluation, and completing initial City probation.&nbsp; An incumbent who fails to complete the training and noncompetitive, criteria-based promotion within two years of hire may be transferred, demoted, or terminated.&nbsp; &nbsp;This class is FLSA nonexempt. Please ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Electrical Controls Supervisor]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 18 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/electrical-controls-supervisor-mesa-841.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=841&amp;role=Electrical+Controls+Supervisor&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[First review of applications will be on Monday, December 8, 2025, and weekly thereafter.&nbsp; The Electrical Controls Supervisor (ECS) is responsible for supervising skilled electrical control specialists engaged in the construction, installation, maintenance, and repair of a variety of industrial electrical/electronic controls, telemetering devices, and medium voltage electrical equipment up to 15kv, utilized to operate and monitor the City’s water, wastewater, and gas systems. &nbsp;The ECS also oversees the following critical functions: &nbsp;assisting in the start-up, commissioning, and troubleshooting of electrical equipment and process control system, including fiber optic networks; providing technical and inspection assistance to City construction inspectors; serving as in-house technical expert for electrical and instrumentation design on new projects by reviewing drawings, plans, specifications, and submittals for gas, water, and wastewater facilities; calibrating and verifying for Arizona Corporation Commission on gas regulator stations; and certifying calibration for Inter-Agency flow meters. Additionally, the ECS performs the following supervisory and program management functions for the Water Resources Department: &nbsp;evaluating bids and managing contracts for the procurement of electrical services, professional services, materials and equipment; preparing, updating, and enforcing electrical and instrumentation specifications for use by City Engineering Department and consultants; assisting in asset management by overseeing process control data entry; responding to service requests from Water Operations and Gas Engineering groups; verifying and processing invoices related to Electrical Contracts; managing the annual operation and maintenance budget for process control group; participating in Capital Improvement Projects (CIP) planning and developing a replacement program for major electrical equipment; establishing internal standard operating procedu]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Water Resources Plant Operator Trainee/I/II/III - Wastewater Treatment]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 11 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/water-resources-plant-operator-traineeiiiiii-wastewater-treatment-mesa-844.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=844&amp;role=Water+Resources+Plant+Operator+Trainee/I/II/III+-+Wastewater+Treatment&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Hiring Bonus: The Water Resources Department is excited to offer a hiring bonus for individuals newly hired as Water Resources Plant Operator Trainee/I/II/III. &nbsp;New Water Resources Operator's may be eligible for a $3,500 incentive at the conclusion of Initial City Probation. &nbsp;To receive the bonus, an Operator must work as a Plant Operator for one year and receive a successful performance evaluation. &nbsp; This recruitment will be used to fill current vacancies at a Wastewater Treatment plant at either the Operator Trainee, I, II or III level; however, t his recruitment will also be used to create a list to fill possible future vacancies&nbsp; at any level. &nbsp; Offer ing salary may be made above the minimum of the posted salary range for this position depending upon qualifications and experience. &nbsp;Employees may progress through the full salary range, subject to their successful performance and annual budget approval.&nbsp; First review of applications will be Monday, October 13, 2025; then weekly thereafter until all&nbsp; vacancies &nbsp;are filled. Water Resources Plant Operator Trainee ($41,660.94 - &nbsp;$57,06.93) A Water Resources Plant Operator Trainee is responsible for learning the basic technical aspects related to the operations and basic maintenance of the Wastewater Treatment plants. &nbsp;A trainee shall receive hands-on training by assisting with and participating in wastewater treatment plant processes for operations, maintenance, and analytical laboratory testing. &nbsp;Duties include assisting with plant operations and basic equipment maintenance including all processes related to the treatment of wastewater. &nbsp;All Water Resources Plant Operator Trainee’s shall use appropriate safety equipment and follow safety procedures in performing assignments. &nbsp;Trainees have the potential to be exposed to job related hazards such as toxic chemicals, chlorine gas, ozone, raw sewage, sludge, and adverse weather conditions. &nbsp;This c]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Facilities Management Superintendent]]></title>
    <date>Mon, 02 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/facilities-management-superintendent-mesa-846.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=846&amp;role=Facilities+Management+Superintendent&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The Facilities Management Department is responsible for the maintenance and operation of more than five (5) million square feet of the City of Mesa’s vertical assets and exterior facilities. This responsibility is carried out through a combination of contracted services and City personnel who specialize in a wide range of building systems and skilled trades, including HVAC, building automation systems, plumbing, electrical, roofing, locksmith services, carpentry, and irrigation systems. This position plays a critical role in coordinating and communicating with building occupants and tenants, as well as supporting the establishment and administration of lease agreements. This classification has been designated as a non-classified, non-merit system, at-will position. &nbsp; First review of applications will be Monday, January 26, 2026, and weekly thereafter as needed. A Facilities Management (FM) Superintendent is responsible for supervising and overseeing construction, maintenance, and special repair of municipal buildings, community facilities, and related public buildings. &nbsp;Supervisory duties include planning, organizing, coordinating, instructing, and evaluating the work of employees involved in special maintenance and repair activities. &nbsp;Administrative responsibilities include: &nbsp;preparation and monitoring of the facilities maintenance budgets; developing, monitoring, and enforcing equipment and facility maintenance contracts; coordinating staff training; developing/revising and implementing section policies; developing and recommending priorities for asset management tasks such as preventative maintenance, repairs, and replacement; developing goals, plans, and performance measures; and serving as liaison with special interest groups, building liaisons, and other City staff to avoid conflict between required maintenance and development activity. &nbsp;This classification is responsible for supervising and overseeing trades and technical work in carp]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Water Resources Field Maintenance Specialist I/II]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 07 Ja</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/water-resources-field-maintenance-specialist-iii-mesa-853.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=853&amp;role=Water+Resources+Field+Maintenance+Specialist+I/II&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The current vacancy may be filled at either the Specialist I or Specialist II level. &nbsp;Offering salary may be made above the minimum of the posted salary range for this position, depending upon qualifications and experience. &nbsp;Employees may progress through the full salary range, subject to their successful performance and annual budget approval.&nbsp; First review of applications will be Monday, November 24, 2025, and weekly thereafter as needed. Water Resources Field Maintenance Specialist I ($48,134.53 - $72,855.12 annually) The Water Resources Field Maintenance Specialist I is a trainee classification in which the incumbent learns to perform specialized work involving the installation, maintenance, and repair of remote water treatment equipment and facilities. &nbsp;An employee in this class accompanies and observes a lead person, specifically the Water Resources Field Maintenance Specialist II and/or Water Resources Field Maintenance Crew Leader class, thus performing daily activities and assisting in performing entry-level water pump system maintenance work. &nbsp;Some examples of duties learned and performed include: &nbsp;performing plumbing work including cutting, threading, and welding pipe; installing and replacing pumps, compressors, motors, and related equipment; lubricating bearings; replacing seals, gaskets, springs, and gears; installing, maintaining, and repairing equipment and facilities, including but not limited to: &nbsp;pumps, compressors, pipes, aeration/mixer equipment, and chlorine equipment, including gaseous and/or onsite generation; and chemical analyzers and dosing equipment, valves, gear boxes, tanks, and swing arms, etc. &nbsp;As the incumbent demonstrates the ability to perform the full range of the proposed Water Resources Field Maintenance Specialist II duties, the complexity and difficulty of assignments will increase. &nbsp;This class performs related duties as required.&nbsp; This class is distinguished from the Water Res]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist I/II- Reclamation]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 16 De</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/water-resources-plant-maintenance-specialist-iii-reclamation-mesa-855.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=855&amp;role=Water+Resources+Plant+Maintenance+Specialist+I/II-+Reclamation&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The current recruitment will be used to fill current vacancies in the Water Reclamation Plant Assignment at either the Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist I or Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist II level. &nbsp; Employees may progress through the full salary range, subject to their successful performance and annual budget approval.&nbsp; &nbsp; The first review of applications will be on Monday, September 22 , 2025 and weekly&nbsp; thereafter as needed. &nbsp; &nbsp; Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist I ($47,757.84 – $66,070.16 annually) A Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist I is a one-year assignment where incumbents function as a trainee and are responsible for learning how to and begin to maintain the City of Mesa’s water reclamation or water treatment plants (depending on assignment) . &nbsp;An employee in this class accompanies and observes a lead person, specifically the Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist II and/or III class, thus performing daily activities and assisting in performing entry-level work. &nbsp;As the incumbent demonstrates the ability to perform the full range of the proposed Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist I duties, the complexity and difficulty of assignments will increase. &nbsp;During this one-year assignment the incumbent must meet requirements and expectations outlined in the criteria-based promotion document. &nbsp;In addition, the incumbent must complete these requirements and proceed to the Water Resources Plant Maintenance Specialist II classification within the one-year time frame. &nbsp;This class performs related duties as required.&nbsp; Water Reclamation Plant Assignment: &nbsp; Incumbents may be assigned to either the Southeast, Northwest, or Greenfield Water Reclamation Plants. &nbsp;Entry-level work will consist of plant maintenance work. &nbsp;Some examples of duties learned and performed include:&nbsp; installing, maintaining, and repairing equipment and facilities]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Utilities Distribution Shift Leader]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 09 De</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/utilities-distribution-shift-leader-mesa-856.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=856&amp;role=Utilities+Distribution+Shift+Leader&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[First review of applications will be on Monday, November 24, 2025. The Utilities Distribution Shift Leader is responsible for supervising and participating in the activities of the Utilities Control Center. &nbsp;The employee in this class supervises, completes performance evaluations, schedules, assigns tasks, coordinates, and reviews the work of Utilities Distribution Controllers and Operators who: &nbsp;monitor the City’s water, gas, wastewater and electric systems; respond to emergencies and alarms; dispatch field staff; operate and control the water system pumping, storage, and pressures; and staff the 24/7 emergency hotline for all four utilities and provide coverage for multiple city departments for afterhours and weekend calls and dispatch. &nbsp;The employee in this class is the first point of escalation for internal and external customers that interact with the Utilities Control Room and is expected to handle these situations with professionalism and tact. &nbsp;The Utilities Distribution Shift Leader is expected to exhibit leadership, facilitate teamwork, schedule training, and provide clear written and verbal communication to Controllers and Operators to ensure: &nbsp;consistent, energy efficient, and reliable system operation; and appropriate response to alarms, emergencies, and inquiries following established protocols. &nbsp;The employee in this class performs related duties as required. This class is distinguished from the Utilities Distribution Controller class by having greater decision-making authority, as well as supervisory responsibility over the Controllers. This class is supervised by the Utilities Control Center Supervisor who reviews the employee's work through meetings, conferences, and reports regarding results achieved and problems encountered. &nbsp;This class must be available on a rotating basis, 24/7, to answer questions regarding unique, abnormal, or emergency situations in the control room.&nbsp; This position is subject to call-ou]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Designer]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 25 No</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/engineering-designer-mesa-858.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=858&amp;role=Engineering+Designer&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The current vacancies are for the NCU and CIP Assignments; however, this recruitment will be used to establish an eligible list to fill possible future vacancies in other assignment areas.&nbsp; First review of applications will be on Monday, October 20th, 2025, and weekly thereafter .&nbsp; Under general direction, an Engineering Designer performs professional engineering work &nbsp;(by assignment)&nbsp; entailing design, plan review, inspections, and related work as required. &nbsp;Employees in this class will independently be responsible for design and project management duties, whether the project is designed in-house or by a consultant. &nbsp;Employees in this class may oversee and direct consultants and personnel in the design of capital improvement projects. &nbsp;Employees may also assist with the review and approval of other types of projects. &nbsp;An Engineering Designer uses independent discretion and judgement with their assigned projects from the initial determination of the scope of work, to the completed construction stage in order to attain the desired results. The Engineering Designer will be assigned projects that range in scope from standard to more difficult and complex designs and may include the design of public work improvements or installation of facilities such as: &nbsp;sanitary sewers, storm drains, street improvements, retention basins, site improvements, building remodels, parks, and new buildings. &nbsp;Duties may involve drafting both 2D and 3D designs of piping systems, utilities, roadways, and other infrastructure systems for the City’s Capital Improvement Program (CIP) using Computer-Aided Design (CAD) programs; resolving design related problems by performing calculations, evaluating alternatives, and/or interviewing affected parties; writing project specific conditions and construction notes; and preparing project specifications and design criteria. &nbsp;This class will independently prepare bid documents; create cost estimates; ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Planner - Long-Range Transportation Planning Assignment]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 04 No</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-planner-long-range-transportation-planning-assignment-mesa-859.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=859&amp;role=Senior+Planner+-+Long-Range+Transportation+Planning+Assignment&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This current vacancy is for the Transportation Assignment. &nbsp; First review of applications will be on Monday, November 3, 2025.&nbsp; A Senior Planner performs advanced-level professional planning work of considerable difficulty and manages complex planning projects to completion. &nbsp;Areas of assignment may include current planning, long-range planning, long-range transportation planning, urban design, and transportation planning. &nbsp;Employees in this class may also serve as a staff liaison for regional and local planning agencies and City boards such as the Planning and Zoning Board, Design Review Board, or Board of Adjustment depending upon assignment. Long-Range Transportation Planning Assignment: Conducts research on best practices and collects and analyzes transportation and land use data to identify transportation needs and support the City’s mobility goals. Reviews and interpret reports, plans, and studies to inform recommendations and evaluate potential impacts to the transportation network. Reviews development proposals for consistency with City plans, policies, and standards by interpreting site plans, schematics, and technical drawings. Implements assigned elements of the Mesa General Plan, Mesa Transportation Master Plan, and other transportation plans and studies. Researches and identifies grant opportunities to support transportation planning goals and coordinate with Planning Division staff on zoning amendments as they relate to transportation and land use planning. Responsibilities for assignments within Planning may include : &nbsp;lead expert in area of responsibility; developing, managing, and implementing land use planning initiatives, policies, and design guidelines; developing, managing, and implementing urban design and placemaking initiatives and policies; developing, managing, preparing, and implementing general and long-range plans; preparing general plan amendment recommendations; analysis of demographic and census data; research]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Network IT Engineer II (Police)]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 28 Oc</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/network-it-engineer-ii-police-mesa-860.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=860&amp;role=Network+IT+Engineer+II+(Police)&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This vacancy is in the Police Department's Information Technology (PDIT) unit for the Infrastructure/Enterprise Operations Assignment, specifically Network Infrastructure.&nbsp; &nbsp; First review of applications will be Monday, September 15, 2025. Police Network Infrastructure Assignment: &nbsp; Plans, assesses, and proactively monitors platform and environment to meet performance and availability metrics. &nbsp;Plans, coordinates, and ensures firmware and software configurations are in place, and monitors performance of specific areas under primary responsibility by proactively taking preemptive measures to minimize interruptions. &nbsp;Documents actions performed to improve skill transfer/knowledge transfer to secondary in support. &nbsp;Performs complex diagnostics and troubleshooting in support of designated platforms. &nbsp;Excels at test scripts and QA processes resulting in increased percentage of successfully implemented changes. &nbsp;The Information Technology (IT) Engineer II in this assignment is expected to have an expert understanding of network protocols, security, routing, switching, and firewall technologies, and mentors and actively shares this expertise with others. &nbsp;Secondary IT disciplines to be supported within this assignment include Server OS and virtualization, enterprise storage, and enterprise backup. The ideal candidate shall possess a Cisco Certified Network Professional (CCNP) certification or equivalent experience. The IT Engineer II class provides skilled technical services in support of installation, configuration, testing, integration, and ongoing support for City applications or infrastructure, requiring an in-depth knowledge of the City’s platforms and environment in support of meeting availability and performance goals. &nbsp;This class applies to Business Solutions and Application Development; Business Analytics; Database; Desktop and Mobile Services; Service Desk; GIS (Geographic Information System); Network; Security; U]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Cdl Driver</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Application Support Engineer II]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 21 Oc</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/it-application-support-engineer-ii-mesa-861.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=861&amp;role=IT+Application+Support+Engineer+II&amp;company=City+of+Mesa</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Mesa]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Mesa’s Department of Innovation and Technology (DoIT) is hiring for two (2) current vacancies.&nbsp; One vacancy is in the Application Support (Utility Services) , and one is in the ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) Assignment. The first review of applications will be on Monday, August 25, 2025, and weekly thereafter. The Information Technology (IT) Engineer II class provides skilled technical services in support of installation, configuration, testing, integration, and ongoing support for City applications or infrastructure requiring an in-depth knowledge of the City’s platforms and environment in support of meeting availability and performance goals.&nbsp; This class applies to Business Solutions and Application Development; Business Analytics; Database; Desktop and Mobile Services; Service Desk; Geographic Information System (GIS); Network; Security; Unified Communications; and Server, Storage, and Backup. Common duties include:&nbsp; performing work on multiple assignments simultaneously such as configuration, integration, development, testing, and resolution of problems for systems; assessing, troubleshooting, and following established guidelines in the escalation of hardware, software, and networking problems; initiating and/or maintaining Incident Reports (IRs) using an on-line incident management system; assisting with research, evaluation, and implementation of new technologies and/or packaged software; installing and supporting hardware and/or software; preparing and/or updating system documentation; controlling changes in system environments to ensure stable and reliable delivery of computer resources; coordinating and mentoring staff; developing and analyzing data for problem resolution and strategic planning; implementing, maintaining, and monitoring systems and their related subsystems; participating in projects and/or leading small- to medium-scale projects and activities related to City computer systems, data, and infrastructure; partici]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Cdl Driver</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Public Works & Utilities Assistant Director]]></title>
    <date>Fri, 13 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/public-works-amp-utilities-assistant-director-chandler-866.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=866&amp;role=Public+Works+&amp;+Utilities+Assistant+Director&amp;company=City+of+Chandler</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Chandler]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Chandler Public Works &amp; Utilities Department is seeking qualified individuals interested in joining our team as a&nbsp; Public Works &amp; Utilities Assistant Director, assigned to Utilities. This is a full-time, exempt position with benefits, serving at the pleasure of the Public Works &amp; Utilities Director and the City Manager. This is an on-site position working Monday through Friday.&nbsp; Why work for Chandler? • Open and collaborative environment • Up to 8 hours paid time off annually to volunteer in the community • Dress code is business casual, with jeans on Fridays • 3 medical plans to choose from, along with dental and vision coverage • Accrue 130 hours of paid vacation in your first year, eligible for use immediately following accrual • Accrue 96 hours of paid sick leave in your first year, eligible for use immediately following accrual • 12 paid holidays annually, with the potential for additional holiday leave at the end of 2026, subject to approval by the City Manager • Become part of the Arizona State Retirement System with a 100% city contribution match • City contributions of 1% gross wages per pay period to deferred compensation &nbsp; • Robust Employee Wellness program with $350 incentive • Professional development opportunities • Tuition reimbursement up to $5,250 annually • Free Tumbleweed Recreation Center membership • Flexible schedule/remote work options (when available) &nbsp; City of Chandler Chandler, Arizona, known as the Community of Innovation, is a vibrant and welcoming city that blends diversity, creativity, and a strong sense of community pride. With a population of more than 291,000, Chandler has grown into the fourth-largest city in Arizona and the 76th-largest in the nation. Situated in the heart of Maricopa County, with a population of more than 4.5 million, Chandler is a neighbor to the capital city of Phoenix.&nbsp; Chandler offers an outstanding quality of life for residents of all ages. Families enjoy top-r]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Housing and Redevelopment Senior Manager]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 10 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/housing-and-redevelopment-senior-manager-chandler-869.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=869&amp;role=Housing+and+Redevelopment+Senior+Manager&amp;company=City+of+Chandler</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Chandler]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Chandler Neighborhood Resources Department is currently seeking qualified individuals interested in joining our team as a Housing and Redevelopment Senior Manager [PHA Director ] . &nbsp;The position is scheduled to work 5 days, 8 hours. &nbsp; Current City of Chandler employees may only hold one position and are not eligible for additional part-time or secondary positions within the City of Chandler. Why work for Chandler? • Open and collaborative environment • Up to 8 hours paid time off annually to volunteer in the community • Dress code is business casual, with jeans on Fridays • 3 medical plans to choose from along with dental and vision coverage • Accrue 130 hours paid vacation in your first year, eligible for use immediately following accrual • Accrue 96 hours paid sick leave in your first year, eligible for use immediately following accrual • 12 paid holidays annually, with the potential for additional holiday leave the end of 2026, subject to approval by the City Manager • Become part of the Arizona State Retirement System with a 100% city contribution match • City contributions of 1% gross wages per pay period to deferred compensation &nbsp; • Robust Employee Wellness program with $350 incentive • Professional development opportunities • Tuition reimbursement up to $5,250 annually, $3,200 for part time employees • Free Tumbleweed Recreation Center membership • Flexible schedule/remote work options (when available) Who we are The City of Chandler Public Housing Authority is administered by the City’s Housing and Redevelopment Division. &nbsp;Our primary focus is to provide safe and affordable housing to participating individuals and families with a high level of customer service. &nbsp;The Division also partners with other supportive services in the community that empower our participants to thrive. The Division is responsible for the management of site-based and scattered site public housing units, the Housing Choice Voucher program, as well as]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Intern (Water PIO)]]></title>
    <date>Tue, 10 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/intern-water-pio-scottsdale-886.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=886&amp;role=Intern+(Water+PIO)&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Please note: Due to this position being part-time, the classification is unclassified, meaning it is at-will and serves at the discretion of the City. These positions have limited benefits. At Scottsdale Water, we pride ourselves on delivering superior quality water and service to the Scottsdale community. Our employees ensure a safe, sustainable drinking water system, operate an innovative water reclamation system and help Scottsdale Water consistently maintain its position as one of the nation’s most advanced and efficient water utilities. We value our employees and challenge them to constantly improve how we do business. Our team is made up of professionals from all disciplines – engineering, finance, operations, laboratory science, chemistry, public relations, hydrology, customer service, electrical, maintenance and so much more. Click&nbsp; here &nbsp;to be directed to the Scottsdale Water Careers webpage. About the Position: Provides professional level staff and/or public assistance in the areas of research and analysis, procedural studies, program coordination, and technical planning for a variety of general administrative or specialized technical projects in support of the objectives of the division to which assigned. Anticipated starting salary for this position may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity. The full salary range is listed above and mid-point for this position is $24.08/hour.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Division Finance Manager]]></title>
    <date>Mon, 09 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/division-finance-manager-scottsdale-887.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=887&amp;role=Division+Finance+Manager&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Under the general direction of Division management, this position performs financial work which may include coordinating the development of financial plans and/or the Division’s operating budget, capital improvement program and related funding plans, grants and special revenue funds. &nbsp;Performs advanced professional level and technical duties for budgetary and financial activities as well as directing or participating in gathering information, making statistical analysis and studying and resolving special administrative problems. This position will be assigned to the Police Department.&nbsp; Anticipated starting salary may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity. The midpoint of the salary range is $120,536.00 annually. In order to be considered for this position, the department requests that you attach a Cover Letter &amp; Resume to your application. Benefits Highlights: The City of Scottsdale offers a comprehensive benefits package including: 12 Paid Holidays, which includes 1 Floating Holiday Vacation Accrual; starts at 10.3 hours/month Sick Leave Accrual; 8 hours/month Medical (which includes behavioral health coverage), Dental and Vision Benefits City Paid Basic Life Insurance (equal to one times employee annual salary); option of Supplemental Life Insurance Tuition Reimbursement; $2,500/year Participation in the Arizona State Retirement System (ASRS) Defined benefit plan with mandatory employer and employee contributions currently at 12% which includes a Long-Term Disability benefit Supplemental Retirement Plans through Nationwide; 457&nbsp; Pet Insurance Bilingual pay compensation Employer contribution of $10 per pay period to employee's PEHP (Post-Employment Health Plan) account &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Please visit the&nbsp; Human Resources and Benefits Information &nbsp;page for more information.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Summer Intern - City Treasurer's Office]]></title>
    <date>Mon, 09 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/summer-intern-city-treasurerx27s-office-scottsdale-888.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=888&amp;role=Summer+Intern+-+City+Treasurer&#x27;s+Office&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Provides professional level staff and/or public assistance in the areas of research and analysis, procedural studies, program coordination, and technical planning for a variety of general administrative or specialized technical projects in support of the objectives of the division to which assigned. This intern will work in the city's Budget office starting in early June and ending in mid-August. This is a part-time, temporary position with no benefits.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Department Systems Analyst Programmer III / II/ I (Part time Underfill Opportunity)]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/department-systems-analyst-programmer-iii-ii-i-part-time-underfill-opportunity-s.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=889&amp;role=Department+Systems+Analyst+Programmer+III+/+II/+I+(Part+time+Underfill+Opportunity)&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Under direction of assigned supervisor, manager or director ,&nbsp; provides complex analytical support, maintenance and/or modification of existing systems and development of new modules/functions in one or more areas/systems. Provides coordination with the Information Technology Department serving as liaison between business users and information technology staff, vendors and service providers; and performs related work as required.&nbsp; This position will be for the Budget Department in the City Treasurer’s Office, focusing on reporting in Oracle Fusion. &nbsp;Normal daily duties may include Project management, systems analysis, Oracle OTBI and BI Publisher report writing, as well as responding to questions, writing requirements, and implementing solutions for the Budget team in Oracle EPM. &nbsp; Please note: T his position is part-time, and unclassified, meaning it is at-will and serves at the discretion of the City. These positions have limited benefits as required by law. It is not a remote position . Applicants who do not meet all the minimum requirements for the Department Systems Analyst/Programmer III position may be considered for an underfill as a Department Systems Analyst II or I, depending on applicant qualifications. If the position is underfilled, the salary offered would be commensurate with the lower level classification. The minimum requirements and salary range for the underfill position are listed below in the minimum qualification section .&nbsp; Anticipated starting salary for this position may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity. Although the full salary range is listed above, the salary range to midpoint for each position is listed below. &nbsp; Please note: Be sure to check your email junk/spam folders regularly for possible notifications and/or self-schedule interview invitations from Governmentjobs.com.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Water Electrician II (W/WW Electrician II)]]></title>
    <date>Wed, 25 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/water-electrician-ii-www-electrician-ii-scottsdale-895.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=895&amp;role=Water+Electrician+II+(W/WW+Electrician+II)&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[At Scottsdale Water, we pride ourselves on delivering superior quality water and service to the Scottsdale community. Our employees ensure a safe, sustainable drinking water system, operate an innovative water reclamation system and help Scottsdale Water consistently maintain its position as one of the nation’s most advanced and efficient water utilities. We value our employees and challenge them to constantly improve how we do business. Our team is made up of professionals from all disciplines – engineering, finance, operations, laboratory science, chemistry, public relations, hydrology, customer service, electrical, maintenance and so much more. Click&nbsp; here&nbsp; to be directed to the Scottsdale Water Careers webpage. About the Position Performs industrial journey-level electrical, electronic and computer work in the installation, maintenance and repair of the City's water and wastewater systems and equipment. Anticipated starting salary for this position may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity. &nbsp;The full salary range is listed above and mid-point for this position is $41.18/hour.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Fleet Technician]]></title>
    <date>Fri, 20 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/fleet-technician-scottsdale-897.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=897&amp;role=Fleet+Technician&amp;company=City+of+Scottsdale</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Scottsdale]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This classification performs maintenance and light repairs on a wide variety of automotive and heavy equipment. The incumbent assists Fleet Mechanics and Fleet Mechanic Seniors while performing a variety of general repairs and maintenance on widely diverse equipment and vehicles. Anticipated starting salary may be up to mid-point depending on candidate’s experience and internal equity.&nbsp; The full salary range is listed above and mid-point for this position is $26.54 per hour. The City of Scottsdale Fleet department is committed to hiring and maintaining a high-performance team. &nbsp;In an effort to do so, we offer a competitive additional compensation program for those who have and maintain current and qualifying ASE and EVT Certifications as well as reimburse for passed qualifying ASE/EVT Certification testing. &nbsp;Employees can earn up to an additional $5,000 annually for certifications above and beyond what is required for the position. &nbsp;This program is based on budget availability each fiscal year.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[RECREATION COORDINATOR - AQUATICS]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 12 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/recreation-coordinator-aquatics-surprise-902.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=902&amp;role=RECREATION+COORDINATOR+-+AQUATICS&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Surprise Parks &amp; Recreation Department is seeking a dynamic, motivated Aquatics professional to lead, elevate, and expand our swim lesson programs and water safety initiatives. We’re looking for someone who brings genuine enthusiasm for water safety, strong communication skills, and a commitment to creating exceptional learning experiences for swimmers of all ages. This position is ideal for someone who thrives in a high-volume, organized program environment, values collaboration, and takes pride in delivering high-quality aquatic programs to the community.&nbsp; A strong passion for aquatics and staff development is essential, along with the ability to strengthen learn-to-swim programs through thoughtful planning, effective scheduling, and comprehensive staff training. Join us in protecting our community and shaping a positive, educational, and fun aquatic environment. SUMMARY Incumbents provide skilled professional recreation programming for a geographic area, several specialty fields, or a major facility. &nbsp;Assignment may include providing Citywide programming in several specialty fields such as special events, aquatics, special interest classes, adaptive, youth and adult sports, tennis, youth council, civic engagement initiatives, and teens. &nbsp;Incumbents develop and coordinate a variety of Citywide classes, programs, and events for citizens of all ages; coordinate, implement, maintain, and evaluate programs; and may oversee facility operations. &nbsp;Responsibilities include preparing and coordinating the master schedule; staffing specific programs, including the recruitment of instructors and officials; and supervising part time staff and volunteers. &nbsp;Incumbents also perform administrative duties such as compiling data, maintaining program budget, preparing reports, soliciting bids, and providing quality customer service. EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE Bachelor's Degree in Recreation or a related field, and three years related experien]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[BUSINESS MANAGER- FINANCIAL]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/business-manager-financial-surprise-915.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=915&amp;role=BUSINESS+MANAGER-+FINANCIAL&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The City of Surprise is a fast-growing community where strong financial leadership is essential to turning plans into reality. As a Business Manager - Financial, you’ll play a central role in developing and managing department budgets, analyzing complex financial data, and supporting oversight of the development agreements and contracts that shape the City’s future. This role is ideal for someone with strong skills in Excel for purposes of reconciling data from multiple sources and translating complex financial information into clear deliverables. You’ll work in a collaborative, solutions-oriented environment where finance is a strategic partner. If you enjoy digging into details, improving processes, and using your technical skills to support responsible growth and high-quality public services, the City of Surprise offers the opportunity to make a visible and lasting impact. SUMMARY Incumbents are responsible for supervising staff, oversight and managing functions within their assigned areas with supervision from the Assistant Director. When assigned as the Business Manager - Financial, this includes completing and monitoring all financial transactions and Development Agreements; participating in department audits; preparing, monitoring, and analyzing Department budgets; analyzing operations of the various Department programs; managing grants, contracts and IGA’s; and preparing financial and budget impact analysis and statements regarding possible program and operational changes within the Department.&nbsp; EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE &nbsp; Bachelor’s Degree in a related field and five years of technical experience, including three years of supervisory or lead experience; or an equivalent combination of education and experience sufficient to successfully perform the essential duties of the job such as those listed above. &nbsp;Additional education cannot be substituted for experience. CERTIFICATIONS, LICENSES, REGISTRATIONS &nbsp; None SELECTION PROCESS Applicants]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[CITY AUDITOR]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/city-auditor-surprise-916.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=916&amp;role=CITY+AUDITOR&amp;company=City+of+Surprise</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Surprise]]></company>
    <city>Surprise</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[WE ARE SEEKING Our ideal candidate is a&nbsp;principled audit leader&nbsp;with deep expertise in municipal finance and&nbsp;Yellow Book (GAGAS) standards. They possess a sophisticated understanding of complex audit controls and a proven track record in both financial and operational analysis. As a&nbsp;strategic communicator, they bring an extensive professional reporting background necessary to drive public transparency and provide clear, actionable insights to City leadership. ABOUT THE CITY AUDITOR The City Auditor is a City Council appointed position, responsible for conducting independent appraisals and strategic evaluation as part of the city’s audit program and annual audit plan, providing a clear and unbiased line of communication to the Mayor and City Council. &nbsp;The City Auditor will bring transparency, objectivity, and accountability in financial, performance, and attestation engagements covering internal controls and compliance. &nbsp; &nbsp; To provide for the independence of the city audit program, the city auditor will be an appointed official functionally reporting to the audit committee. &nbsp;The City Auditor leads a professional staff which includes a Senior Internal Auditor and Internal Auditor. City Auditor's Mission Statement:&nbsp; To provide independent, objective, accurate and timely auditing services that are designed to improve operations, cultivate transparency and accountability. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES The duties listed below are intended only as general illustrations of the various types of work that may be performed. Specific statements of duties not included do not exclude them from the position if the work is similar, related, or a logical assignment to the position.&nbsp; Appoints, supervises, directs, disciplines, and terminates employees under the supervision of the city auditor Complies will all city policies and procedures of the city unless inconsistent with Municipal Code Develops a flexible, risk-based inter]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Deputy Finance Director]]></title>
    <date>Fri, 13 Fe</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/deputy-finance-director-buckeye-951.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=951&amp;role=Deputy+Finance+Director&amp;company=City+of+Buckeye</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Buckeye]]></company>
    <city>Buckeye</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Administrative Assistant]]></title>
    <date>Thu, 05 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/administrative-assistant-apache-junction-959.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=959&amp;role=Administrative+Assistant&amp;company=City+of+Apache+Junction</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[City of Apache Junction]]></company>
    <city>Apache Junction</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[(Anticipated hiring range $21.64 - $22.73/hr) Positions assigned to this class perform a variety of administrative and clerical support duties involved in the day-to-day operations of a department. Incumbents assist in the preparation and administration of the annual budget and time and attendance processing. Work involves service to the public and office support as needed. Specific tasks vary depending on area of assignment.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Public Works Operations Manager (Transportation/Traffic)]]></title>
    <date>Sat, 07 Ma</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/public-works-operations-manager-transportationtraffic-queen-creek-975.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=975&amp;role=Public+Works+Operations+Manager+(Transportation/Traffic)&amp;company=Town+of+Queen+Creek</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Town of Queen Creek]]></company>
    <city>Queen Creek</city>
    <state>AZ</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This position will be responsible for managing the Streets Maintenance, Pavement Preservation, and administrative staff in our Public Works Department. A background in Engineering is helpful for this role as well as project management and contract management.&nbsp; This job classification description is intended to be generic in nature and not an exhaustive list of all duties and responsibilities. &nbsp;The specific tasks/duties may vary based on position assignment and as determined by the Town of Queen Creek. JOB CLASSIFICATION SUMMARY &nbsp; Positions assigned to this class are responsible for administering assigned programs. &nbsp;Incumbents are responsible and accountable for section planning and are charged with program supervision and implementation of services and/or programs. DISTINGUISHING CHARACTERISTICS This is a management level position, recognized as a supervisory and/or organizational authority within a specific discipline and demonstrates specific, broad practical knowledge in a major functional area. &nbsp;Work involves directing, planning and coordinating staff and projects/programs, and budget. Assists with policy development within assigned functional area or the organization. &nbsp; Typically, is a second-level supervisor.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </job>
</source>
