<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
  <publisher>The French Agency</publisher>
  <publisherurl>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs</publisherurl>
  <lastBuildDate>2026-03-09 06:11</lastBuildDate>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[FT Accounts Payable Associate]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/ft-accounts-payable-associate-tempe-136.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=136&amp;role=FT+Accounts+Payable+Associate&amp;company=Included+Health</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Included Health]]></company>
    <city>Tempe</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Title: FT Accounts Payable Associate
About the Role
• Manage and process invoices from vendors and suppliers, ensuring accuracy and timely payments.
• Analyze accounts payable transactions, resolving any discrepancies or issues that may arise.

The Accounts Payable Associate will be responsible for maintaining accurate financial records and reports. This includes tracking expenses and identifying areas for cost savings.
Taking care of our team members with medical, dental & vision benefits as well as 401k match program to help them thrive in all aspects of their life!]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Accountant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-accountant-morristown-135.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=135&amp;role=Senior+Accountant&amp;company=Barron+Lighting+Group</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Barron Lighting Group]]></company>
    <city>Morristown</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[About Barron Lighting Group

Barron Lighting Group values integrity, innovation, quality and flexibility. Our employees are committed to delivering world-class service when our customers need it.
Senior Accountant Role Summary

The Senior Accountant plays a key role in supporting the Accounting Department by ensuring accurate, timely and compliant financial records and reporting. With 5+ years of general accounting experience, this position assists with financial statement preparation, reconciliation and review of balance sheet accounts.]]></description>
    <salary>90000-150000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Entry Level Tax Associate]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/entry-level-tax-associate-mesa-134.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=134&amp;role=Entry+Level+Tax+Associate&amp;company=Jackson+Hewitt</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Jackson Hewitt]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Description:

Joining the Jackson Hewitt team as an Entry Level Tax Associate means becoming a vital resource for your local community during the busiest time of the year. We believe that great service starts with great people, not just a background in math or accounting. In this role, you will guide clients through the complexities of tax season with a focus on empathy and clarity. Whether you are looking to launch a career in finance or simply want a seasonal role that offers professional growth and a flexible schedule, we provide the tools and supportive environment necessary to help you thrive from day one.

Qualifications:
• A natural "people person" who enjoys solving problems and providing top-tier service.
• Clear communication skills, with the ability to break down complex details for others.
• Tech-savvy enough to handle standard office software and learn our internal filing systems.
• The ability to keep a cool head and stay organized when the office pace picks up.
• A high school diploma or equivalent, plus an eagerness to master new tax regulations.

Benefits:
• Hourly pay that rewards your hard work, supplemented by performance-based bonuses.
• Free, industry-leading training to get you fully certified in tax preparation.
• We cover the costs for your PTIN registration and EA certification study resources.
• Work-life balance through adaptable scheduling that fits your lifestyle.
• Exclusive corporate perks and a variety of health and wellness benefits.
• Continuous learning opportunities to keep your skills sharp for future seasons.
• Discounted tax preparation services for your close friends and family.

Responsibilities:
• Meeting one-on-one with clients to understand their unique financial situations.
• Entering data precisely into our tax software to ensure accurate and timely filings.
• Cultivating a loyal client base by providing a dependable and friendly experience.
• Partnering with your local team to maintain a smooth and efficient office wor]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-queen-creek-133.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=133&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Queen Creek</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Accounting Manager

Lead accounting operations and ensure accurate financial reporting in support of renewable energy projects and corporate activities.
• Supervise accounting staff, strengthen internal controls, and partner with cross-functional teams to manage day-to-day accounting functions.
• Maintain financial integrity, supporting operational scalability as the organization grows.]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accountant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accountant-fort-mcdowell-132.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=132&amp;role=Accountant&amp;company=Aldi</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Aldi]]></company>
    <city>Fort McDowell</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Summary of Accountant:

Our store employees work many roles - from Accountant. As a store employee, you're also responsible for merchandising product, monitoring inventory and keeping the store looking its best. It's an opportunity to get more out of your career and grow in an exciting environment. Their hard work makes it possible to uphold our company philosophy, providing quality products at the best possible price. Their smiles and pleasant demeanors keep customers coming back time and time again.Our store employees are the face of the ALDI shopping experience.

Benefits of Accountant:
• We offer a flexible schedule,
• Insurance benefits
• Fast paced exciting work place where you can refine your skills.

Responsibilities of Accountant:
• Conducts customer transactions, fulfills general cleaning obligations, and arranges merchandise presentations and shelf restocking in an orderly fashion
• Provide exceptional customer support by helping clients navigate their shopping journey
• Work together with colleagues and maintain open communication with the store management group]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-sun-city-131.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=131&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Title: Accounting Manager

The Accounting Manager is responsible for overseeing core accounting operations and ensuring accurate, timely, and compliant financial reporting in support of renewable energy projects.

This role manages day-to-day accounting functions, supervises accounting staff, strengthens internal controls, and partners cross-functionally to support project accounting, close processes, and audits.
• Lead a team of accountants by providing guidance training performance feedback development support journal entries account reconciliations month end year end close processes ensuring accurate timely financial reporting in accordance with GAAP company policies regulatory requirements managing reviewing balance sheet income statement reconciliations investigating resolving variances coordinating activities related to renewable energy projects including cost tracking accruals collaboration with project teams supporting the preparation of financial statements management reports adhoc analyses leadership maintaining strengthening internal controls audit readiness accuracy partnering AP AR tax procurement finance teams to ensure endtoend alignment assisting internal external audits documentation explanations responses driving continuous improvement opportunities process optimization automation scalability within operations ERP system enhancements testing implementation process documentation]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-carefree-130.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=130&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Carefree</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Accounting Manager Role

The Accounting Manager at Atlantica plays a key role in maintaining financial integrity and supporting operational scalability as the organization grows.
Key Responsibilities]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-youngtown-129.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=129&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Youngtown</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[As the Accounting Manager at Atlantica, you will oversee core accounting operations and ensure accurate, timely, and compliant financial reporting in support of renewable energy projects and corporate activities. This role manages day-to-day accounting functions, supervises accounting staff, strengthens internal controls, and partners cross-functionally to support project accounting close processes.
• Lead a team of accountants providing guidance training performance feedback development support
• Oversight general ledger activities journal entries account reconciliations month end year end close processes ensuring GAAP compliance company policies regulatory requirements
• Maintain strengthen internal controls audit readiness financial accuracy collaborating AP AR tax procurement finance teams

The ideal candidate has 5+ years progressive accounting experience with at least 2 years supervisory managerial role. Strong working knowledge GAAP financial reporting internal controls proficiency ERP systems Excel skills supporting audits month-end cycles deadlines analytical organizational problem-solving skills high attention detail effective communicator collaboration departments levels organization demonstrated ability lead process improvements accounting automation initiatives.]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accountant]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accountant-webb-128.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=128&amp;role=Accountant&amp;company=Aldi</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Aldi]]></company>
    <city>Webb</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Summary of Accountant:

Our store employees work many roles - from Accountant. As a store employee, you're also responsible for merchandising product, monitoring inventory and keeping the store looking its best. It's an opportunity to get more out of your career and grow in an exciting environment. Their hard work makes it possible to uphold our company philosophy, providing quality products at the best possible price. Their smiles and pleasant demeanors keep customers coming back time and time again.Our store employees are the face of the ALDI shopping experience.

Benefits of Accountant:
• We offer a flexible schedule,
• Insurance benefits
• Fast paced exciting work place where you can refine your skills.

Responsibilities of Accountant:
• Conducts customer transactions, fulfills general cleaning obligations, and arranges merchandise presentations and shelf restocking in an orderly fashion
• Provide exceptional customer support by helping clients navigate their shopping journey
• Work together with colleagues and maintain open communication with the store management group]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-maricopa-127.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=127&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Maricopa</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Accounting Manager

The Accounting Manager plays a key role in maintaining financial integrity and supporting operational scalability as the organization grows. This role is part of a global team working toward common goals at Atlantica.

Key Responsibilities:
• Lead, supervise, and mentor accounting staff, providing guidance, training, performance feedback, and development support.
This includes overseeing general ledger activities,
• journals entries,
• account reconciliations,
, month-end close processes.As required by GAAP company policies and regulatory requirements ensure accurate timely financial reporting.

We believe in a culture of trust shared goals accountability.We operate with one mission no matter where you are based you are part of our team working towards the same goal.]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-manager-waddell-126.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=126&amp;role=Accounting+Manager&amp;company=Atlantica</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Atlantica]]></company>
    <city>Waddell</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Accounting Manager

At Atlantica, we are seeking an experienced Accounting Manager to oversee core accounting operations and ensure accurate, timely, and compliant financial reporting in support of renewable energy projects.
Key Responsibilities:

Lead a team of accountants, providing guidance, training, performance feedback,and development support).
Supervise general ledger activities,]]></description>
    <salary>55000-105000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Accountant - Full-time]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/senior-accountant-full-time-phoenix-125.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=125&amp;role=Senior+Accountant+-+Full-time&amp;company=AAA+Northern+California,+Nevada+&amp;+Utah</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[AAA Northern California, Nevada & Utah]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Work For Us?

+ Great Pay - opportunity to participate in AAA discretionary annual incentive plan or other incentive plans depending upon position

+ 401k Matching – $1 for $1 company match up to 6% of eligible earnings per pay period

+ Benefits – Medical, Dental, Vision, wellness program and more!

+ Paid Holidays

+ Paid Time Off – Team Members accrue paid time off monthly. Depending on position, an additional 24 hours per year are earmarked for volunteer activities.

+ Collaborative Environment – AAA will value your contribution to providing exceptional service to our members

+ Free AAA Classic Membership

+ AAA Product Discounts

+ Tuition Reimbursement Program

.

At AAA, our Team Members strive to deliver amazing service and help our Members outsmart life’s roadblocks. We believe everything you do outside of work adds to who you are at work.

NOTE: This role is hybrid and requires 3 days a week onsite in our Phoenix office.

Job SummaryOur Senior Accountant is responsible for accounting functions to include the development and maintenance of accounting systems, general ledger, asset and liability records and other financial transactions, as well as the reporting of financial and statistical data. The ideal candidate uses advanced accounting concepts and company objectives to resolve complex issues in creative and effective ways.

Our Senior Accountant may function as a team lead and/or coordinate functions of others. They receive assignments in the form of goals and exercise considerable judgment and latitude in obtaining results. Interacts with all levels of staff and external constituents to resolve a wide variety of accounting related issues.Essential Functions• Develops implements and/or maintains one or a combination of general accounting systems.• Applies specialized accounting concepts to perform technical analyses to understand past performance and determine present and future performance and/or resource allocations.• Applies company policies and]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, Technical Accounting]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/manager-technical-accounting-phoenix-124.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=124&amp;role=Manager,+Technical+Accounting&amp;company=Aledade,+Inc.</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Aledade, Inc.]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The Manager of Technical Accounting and SEC Reporting will be responsible for supporting the preparation of US GAAP financials, with anticipated Form 10-K/10-Q in the future. The Manager will collaborate closely across internal departments within Aledade to ensure accuracy, completeness and timeliness of reporting of Aledade's financial results. This should be aware of current activity of the FASB, SEC and other relevant authoritative bodies to support Aledade's accounting policies and financial statement disclosures while researching US GAAP, assisting in the documentation and accounting treatment conclusions for technical accounting matters including revenue recognition, share-based compensation and other complex accounting topics and non-routine areas. Coordination with various external consultants on a number of ongoing and future projects.

We are flexible with respect to geographic location, and the ideal candidate will be comfortable working remotely/work from home within the US or be based from Bethesda, MD office.
Primary Duties:
• Collaborate with Auditors to coordinate the quarterly reviews and the annual audit, and support reporting to the Executive Leadership Team, the Audit Committee of the Board of Directors and other operational leaders as needed
• Perform technical accounting research, analysis, documentation, and enablement of significant or complex accounting matters
• Support preparation of accounting entries for complex matters, including but not limited to revenue recognition, acquisition accounting and stock compensation expense
• Ensure effective controls around the SEC reporting, internal reporting and technical accounting process, and assist in development of internal control framework across the business.
• Develop strong cross-functional relationships and serve as a key business partner to ensure that all transactions are properly reflected in the financial statements
Minimum Qualifications:
• Bachelor's degree in Accounting, Finance, or ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ACCOUNTING SPECIALIST MANAGER - 539102]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/accounting-specialist-manager-539102-phoenix-123.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=123&amp;role=ACCOUNTING+SPECIALIST+MANAGER+-+539102&amp;company=Arizona+Department+of+Corrections</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Arizona Department of Corrections]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[This job was posted by https://www.azjobconnection.gov : For more information, please see: https://www.azjobconnection.gov/jobs/7380101 **ACCOUNTING SPECIALIST MANAGER
• 539102** Job Location: Arizona Correctional Industries (ACI)\ 4441 East McDowell Road\ Phoenix, Arizona 85008\

Salary: \$64,800.00 Grade: 21 Closing Date: 03/18/2026 Job Summary: Do you have at least 3 years of accounting experience in government, corrections, or an institutional environment? Are you a leader with experience in payroll systems, accounts receivable processes, and financial reporting? Join our energetic and diverse Arizona Correctional Industries (ACI) finance team. Apply today and make a difference!\ \ The Arizona Department of Corrections, Rehabilitation & Reentry (ADCRR) is looking for an accountant to join our team as the Accounting Specialist Manager. This position oversees key financial operations with a primary focus on inmate payroll administration, accounts receivable management, and daily accounting functions. Ensures accuracy in financial reporting, compliance with institutional policies, and timely processing of financial transactions. Also supervises accounting support staff, provides leadership, training, and performance oversight to maintain a high standard of accuracy, efficiency, and accountability.\ \ For further information about the Arizona Correctional Industries visit: https://aci.az.gov/ Job Duties: Inmate Payroll Management\
• Administers the full cycle of inmate payroll, including timecard collection, wage calculation, deductions, and disbursements\
• Ensures compliance with federal, state, and institutional regulations governing inmate compensation, maintains accurate payroll records, audits discrepancies, and resolves issues promptly\
• Coordinates with facility supervisors to verify work assignments, hours worked, and eligibility for pay\
• Prepares and distributes payroll reports for internal and external audits, ensuring payroll processes are accurate an]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Accountant</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Registered Nurse - ICU/CCU]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-registered-nurse-icuccu-glendale-122.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=122&amp;role=Travel+Registered+Nurse+-+ICU/CCU&amp;company=Supplemental+Health+Care</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Supplemental Health Care]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Description:Supplemental Health Care is hiring Intensive Care Unit And Cardiac/coronary Care Unit Registered Nurses for travel-only contracts at a partnering hospital in Glendale, Arizona. With 40+ years of experience, we connect nurses to nationwide opportunities with competitive pay, benefits, and dedicated support. Please note - this contract is not available to Arizona residents.Qualifications:Active Compact State RN LicenseBLS certification required (AHA)Experience working in an acute care setting within the past 12 months as a Registered Nurse in the ICU/CCU areaAbility to pass a background check and meet credentialing requirementsAdditional experience/certifications may be requiredTravel RN contracts only, must not be an AZ residentTravel ICU/CCU Registered Nurse Contract Details:Compensation: $1,962 - $2,155 per week *estimateLocation: Glendale, ArizonaContract Length: 13 weeks, with potential for extensionSchedule: 36 hours per week | Every other weekendStart Date: Flexible, based on facility needResponsibilities:Assess, plan, implement, and evaluate patient care in accordance with the standards of professional Intensive Care Unit And Cardiac/coronary Care Unit nursing practiceProvide direct patient care, including medication administration and monitoringCollaborate with physicians, patients, and families to ensure continuity of careDocument all assessments, interventions, and patient responsesWhat We Offer:Full medical, dental, vision, life, and even pet insurance!Round the clock support. No matter where you are or what time it is, Supplemental Health Care is standing by.SHC's Share the Care referral program is the most dynamic, profitable referral program in the industry.401(k) Retirement Savings Program with a wide range of investment options.Discounted and free online access to CEU courses through Supplemental University.Apply online now for immediate consideration and connect with an SHC recruiter to take the next step in your travel nursing career]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Cardiac Rehabilitation Unit]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-cardiac-rehabilitation-unit-sun-city-121.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=121&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Cardiac+Rehabilitation+Unit&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

1100 Central Avenue SE Albuquerque, NM 87106-4930

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Join Our Team!
At Presbyterian, where your work truly matters, we are excited to welcome applicants for the RN position in our Cardiac Step Down unit. Whether you are a new graduate or an experienced Registered Nurse, we encourage you to apply!

New graduates can benefit from our mandatory residency program, featuring engaging monthly seminars led by our Nurse Residency Team, peer-to-peer debriefing sessions, and invaluable mentoring support. This program is designed to facilitate a smooth transition into your nursing career.

Your Growth Matters!
We are committed to your professional development. We offer educational opportunities, career advancement options, tuition reimbursement, scholarship programs, and specialized training. You will also receive a staff safety badge for discreet emergency communication, malpractise liability insurance, and options for loan forgiveness through the New Mexico Higher Education Department.

Type of Opportunity: Full time
FTE: 0.90
Job Exempt: No
Work Shift: 12 Hour Nights (United States of America)

About the Role:
In our 38-bed Cardiac Step Down unit, you will provide exceptional patient-focused care to those requiring telemetry monitoring and treatment for cardiovascular disorders, including cardiac arrhythmias and heart failure. You will care for patients recovering from myocardial infarctions, pacemaker implants, and other critical cardiovascular procedures, collaboratively working within an interdisciplinary team. Our unit, which accommodates approximately 50% progressive care patients, ensures comprehensive care throughout the inpatient stay, followed by personalized discharge planning to support outpatient needs.

Sign-On and Relocation Bonuses Available!

Qualifications:
• Minimum Associate Degree from an accredited nursing program is preferred.
• Current Registered Nurse license in New ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse(RN) Behavioral Health]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nursern-behavioral-health-sacaton-120.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=120&amp;role=Registered+Nurse(RN)+Behavioral+Health&amp;company=Copper+Springs+East</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Copper Springs East]]></company>
    <city>Sacaton</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Copper Springs East

Registered Nurse (RN), Behavioral Health

Full Time | 3x12 | Day Shift 7am-7pm

Your experience matters

Copper Springs - East is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network with facilities coast to coast. We are driven by a profound commitment to prioritize your well-being so you can provide exceptional care to others. As a Registered Nurse (RN), joining our team, you're embracing a vital mission dedicated to making communities healthier ®. Join us on this meaningful journey where your skills, compassion and dedication will make a remarkable difference in the lives of those we serve.

More about our team

Copper Springs in Gilbert, Arizona, is a 96-bed behavioral health hospital. It offers both inpatient and outpatient programs for mental health and addition for adults, and seniors. The facility provides a range of treatments for mental health and addiction issues. Copper Spring is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network committed to making communities healthier® with acute care, rehabilitation, and behavioral health facilities from coast to coast. From your first day to your next career milestone-your experience matters.

How you'll contribute

A Behavioral Health RN who excels in this role:
• Will assess the patient and plan care within set timeframes and document findings according to policies
• Will monitor patient for change of condition and respond accordingly up to and including notification of the physician
• RN will follow hospital policy for medication administration
• RN will consistently use empathy, dignity, and respect when interacting with patients
• Delivery of quality nursing care to ensure that goals of the treatment plan are properly executed following hospital policies and procedures and demonstrated nursing competencies
• Assists/performs comprehensive nursing assessments on all patients

Why join us

We believe that investing in our employees is the first step to providin]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Up to $38,000 Sign-on Bonus]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-up-to-38000-sign-on-bonus-tempe-119.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=119&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Up+to+$38,000+Sign-on+Bonus&amp;company=Federal+Bureau+of+Prisons</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Federal Bureau of Prisons]]></company>
    <city>Tempe</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Summary
Corrections professionals who foster a humane and secure environment and ensure public safety by preparing individuals for successful reentry into our communities.

Duties

Registered Nurse provides direct patient care services in accordance with legal, ethical and institution standards. Provides nursing care of a general nature to inmates in the institution hospital/clinic, and may be provided to patients in specific areas, e.g., psychiatric, operating room, orthopedics, geriatrics, etc. Develops a nursing assessment for each patient, to include planning, implementing, and evaluating nursing care. May assess and identify high risk symptoms/behaviors in patients, to include suicidal risk, homicidal risk and risk for verbal and/or physical abuse. Completes nutritional screening as part of the assessment and refers patient to a dietitian for a nutritional assessment if necessary. Monitors, evaluates and revises the plan of care as needed. May also assess and document the discharge planning needs of a patient. Delegates and coordinates care based on assessments. Along with all other correctional institution employees, incumbent is charged with responsibility for maintaining security of the institution. The staff correctional responsibilities precede all others required by this position and is performed on a regular and recurring basis.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Emergency Department]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-emergency-department-sun-city-118.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=118&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Emergency+Department&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

1010 Spruce Street, Espanola, NM 87532-2724

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Summary:

As a vital member of our healthcare team, you will utilize the nursing process to provide exceptional direct patient care. You will prioritize and efficiently deliver nursing care to an assigned group of patients during your shift, integrating a standards-based framework model.

Why Join Us?
• Opportunities for professional growth, including tuition and certification reimbursement and scholarship options.
• Staff Safety feature: a wearable badge for discreetly calling for help when necessary.
• Incentives for night/weekend shifts, higher education, certifications, and various leadership roles.
• Malpractice liability insurance provided.
• Loan forgiveness opportunities through the New Mexico Higher Education Department.
• Utilization of EPIC electronic charting system.

Job Details:

Type of Opportunity: Full time
FTE: 0.90
Job Exempt: No
Work Shift: Varied Days and Hours (United States of America)

Key Responsibilities:
• Provide direct patient care by assessing, planning, executing, evaluating, and documenting patient needs and responses.
• Collaborate with patients, families, and the healthcare team to coordinate care.
• Conduct assessments in line with unit standards; document accordingly.
• Administer medications and treatments as ordered, following policies and protocols.
• Recognize and address patient and family education needs throughout the care process.
• Demonstrate competence in emergency situations and delegate patient care tasks appropriately.
• Supervise LPNs and non-licensed personnel, providing guidance and leadership.
• Participate in the orientation of new staff and serve as a professional role model.
• Contribute to quality improvement initiatives and maintain positive communication with all team members.

Qualifications:
• Current nursing license in the State of New Mexico or Compact State Nursing License]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse(RN) Behavioral Health]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nursern-behavioral-health-queen-creek-117.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=117&amp;role=Registered+Nurse(RN)+Behavioral+Health&amp;company=Copper+Springs+East</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Copper Springs East]]></company>
    <city>Queen Creek</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Copper Springs East

Registered Nurse (RN), Behavioral Health

Full Time | 3x12 | Day Shift 7am-7pm

Your experience matters

Copper Springs - East is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network with facilities coast to coast. We are driven by a profound commitment to prioritize your well-being so you can provide exceptional care to others. As a Registered Nurse (RN), joining our team, you're embracing a vital mission dedicated to making communities healthier ®. Join us on this meaningful journey where your skills, compassion and dedication will make a remarkable difference in the lives of those we serve.

More about our team

Copper Springs in Gilbert, Arizona, is a 96-bed behavioral health hospital. It offers both inpatient and outpatient programs for mental health and addition for adults, and seniors. The facility provides a range of treatments for mental health and addiction issues. Copper Spring is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network committed to making communities healthier® with acute care, rehabilitation, and behavioral health facilities from coast to coast. From your first day to your next career milestone-your experience matters.

How you'll contribute

A Behavioral Health RN who excels in this role:
• Will assess the patient and plan care within set timeframes and document findings according to policies
• Will monitor patient for change of condition and respond accordingly up to and including notification of the physician
• RN will follow hospital policy for medication administration
• RN will consistently use empathy, dignity, and respect when interacting with patients
• Delivery of quality nursing care to ensure that goals of the treatment plan are properly executed following hospital policies and procedures and demonstrated nursing competencies
• Assists/performs comprehensive nursing assessments on all patients

Why join us

We believe that investing in our employees is the first step to providin]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[RN, Neuro Step Down]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/rn-neuro-step-down-sun-city-116.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=116&amp;role=RN,+Neuro+Step+Down&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:1100 Central Avenue SE Albuquerque, NM 87106-4930

Compensation Pay Range:Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Summary:Love where you work . Our Neuro Step Down unit is hiring an RN looking to specialize in Neuro.

We welcome applications from both new graduates and experienced RNs! New graduates have the opportunity to participate in our mandatory residency program, which includes monthly seminars led by the Nurse Residency Team, peer-to-peer debriefing sessions, support groups/mentoring, and rounding. The Nurse Residency Program is an added benefit designed to support your transition into practice

How you grow, learn and thrive matters here.
Educational and career development options, including tuition and certification reimbursement, scholarship opportunities
Staff Safety (a wearable badge that allows nurses to quickly and discreetly call for help when safety is a concern)
Differentials for night/weekend shifts, higher education, certifications and various lead roles (for eligible positions)
Malpractice liability insurance
Loan forgiveness through the New Mexico Higher Education Department
EPIC electronic charting system Type of Opportunity: Full time FTE: 0.90 Job Exempt: No Work Shift: 12 Hour Nights (United States of America)

Responsibilities:

The Neuro Step Down Unit is hiring a nurse (RN) to join their dedicated team of high-performing nurses that provide exceptional patient care within their 29-bed unit. This unit is highly specialized neurology Step-Down, dedicated to the special care required for patients who are recovering from neurosurgery, or neurological injuries - to include psych patients. Joint Commission-Accredited Primary Step-Down.

Qualifications:
• Minimum Associate Degree: Degree from accredited academic nursing program preferred
• Registered Nurse-NM License
• State of New Mexico or Compact State Nursing License Academic Preparation:
• BLS certification REQUIRED at time of hire.

We're all about well-being, starting]]></description>
    <salary>37-51</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse(RN) Behavioral Health]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nursern-behavioral-health-chandler-heights-115.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=115&amp;role=Registered+Nurse(RN)+Behavioral+Health&amp;company=Copper+Springs+East</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Copper Springs East]]></company>
    <city>Chandler Heights</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Copper Springs East

Registered Nurse (RN), Behavioral Health

Full Time | 3x12 | Day Shift 7am-7pm

Your experience matters

Copper Springs - East is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network with facilities coast to coast. We are driven by a profound commitment to prioritize your well-being so you can provide exceptional care to others. As a Registered Nurse (RN), joining our team, you're embracing a vital mission dedicated to making communities healthier ®. Join us on this meaningful journey where your skills, compassion and dedication will make a remarkable difference in the lives of those we serve.

More about our team

Copper Springs in Gilbert, Arizona, is a 96-bed behavioral health hospital. It offers both inpatient and outpatient programs for mental health and addition for adults, and seniors. The facility provides a range of treatments for mental health and addiction issues. Copper Spring is part of Lifepoint Health, a diversified healthcare delivery network committed to making communities healthier® with acute care, rehabilitation, and behavioral health facilities from coast to coast. From your first day to your next career milestone-your experience matters.

How you'll contribute

A Behavioral Health RN who excels in this role:
• Will assess the patient and plan care within set timeframes and document findings according to policies
• Will monitor patient for change of condition and respond accordingly up to and including notification of the physician
• RN will follow hospital policy for medication administration
• RN will consistently use empathy, dignity, and respect when interacting with patients
• Delivery of quality nursing care to ensure that goals of the treatment plan are properly executed following hospital policies and procedures and demonstrated nursing competencies
• Assists/performs comprehensive nursing assessments on all patients

Why join us

We believe that investing in our employees is the first step to providin]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Long Term Acute Care Registered Nurse]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/long-term-acute-care-registered-nurse-scottsdale-114.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=114&amp;role=Long+Term+Acute+Care+Registered+Nurse&amp;company=Supplemental+Health+Care</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Supplemental Health Care]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Description:Supplemental Health Care is hiring Long Term Acute Care Registered Nurses for contract assignments at a partnering Rehab facility in Scottsdale, Arizona.Whether you're looking to travel or stay local, we're committed to helping Long Term Acute Care RNs find the right fit with top healthcare facilities across the country. With more than 40 years of experience in healthcare staffing, Supplemental Health Care offers reliable support, competitive pay, and great benefits every step of the way.Qualifications:Current Arizona Nursing LicenseAmerican Heart Association BLS2 years of recent relevant nursing experienceLong Term Acute Care RN Contract Details:$1,548 - $1,697 per week*13-week contract with possibility of extensionConsult and coordinate with facility health care team members to assess, plan, implement and evaluate patient care plansAdminister and record prescribed medicationsReport adverse reactions to medications or treatments*Estimated weekly payment may include both taxable wages and tax-free reimbursements for meals, housing, and incidentals. Please speak with a recruiter for details.Apply today to get started with this Long Term Acute Care RN contract opportunity, or talk to our team about the full range of Nursing opportunities available.What We Offer:Full medical, dental, vision, life, and even pet insurance!Round the clock support. No matter where you are or what time it is, Supplemental Health Care is standing by.SHC's Share the Care referral program is the most dynamic, profitable referral program in the industry.401(k) Retirement Savings Program with a wide range of investment options.Discounted and free online access to CEU courses through Supplemental University.Supplemental Health Care is an Equal Opportunity Employer. All candidates, including veterans and those with disabilities, are encouraged to apply. SHC will consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with the requirements of appl]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Observation Unit - RN]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-observation-unit-rn-glendale-113.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=113&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Observation+Unit+-+RN&amp;company=Mayo+Clinic</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Mayo Clinic]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Mayo Clinic

Mayo Clinic is top-ranked in more specialties than any other care provider according to U.S. News & World Report. As we work together to put the needs of the patient first, we are also dedicated to our employees, investing in competitive compensation and comprehensive benefit plans – to take care of you and your family, now and in the future. And with continuing education and advancement opportunities at every turn, you can build a long, successful career with Mayo Clinic.

Benefits Highlights
• Medical: Multiple plan options.
• Dental: Delta Dental or reimbursement account for flexible coverage.
• Vision: Affordable plan with national network.
• Pre-Tax Savings: HSA and FSAs for eligible expenses.
• Retirement: Competitive retirement package to secure your future.

Responsibilities

The registered nurse (RN) is accountable for the coordination of nursing care, including direct patient care, patient/family education and transitions of care. The RN supports professional nursing practice across practice settings and across the continuum of care to meet the needs of the patient and family. The RN will function within the Mayo Clinic Nursing Professional Practice Model, which includes accountability for planning, implementing, evaluating and communicating all phases of nursing care for assigned patients. The ANA Nursing: Scope and Standards of Practice provide a basis for the practice of the RN. The RN provides leadership through activities such as preceptor role, informal and formal leadership roles, and quality improvement efforts. The RN delegates patient care according to skill level, experience, patient acuity, fiscal accountability and availability of resources. The RN possesses excellent communication skills; is skillful in mentoring and teaching; and may participate on committees or projects. A subset of employees may be required to drive their personal vehicle as a part of the responsibility of their role.

This role is eligible for TN sponsors]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Operating Room Registered Nurse PRN]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/operating-room-registered-nurse-prn-paradise-valley-112.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=112&amp;role=Operating+Room+Registered+Nurse+PRN&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Paradise Valley</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address: 2400 Unser Blvd Rio Rancho, NM 87124

Compensation Pay Range: Minimum Offer $41.58 Maximum Offer $56.10

Summary: Join the dynamic surgical services team at Rust Medical Center as an Experienced Registered Nurse (RN) in the Operating Room. We are seeking dedicated professionals who are passionate about patient care and eager to make a difference in our community.

Why Choose Us?
We prioritize your growth and development through educational opportunities, tuition reimbursement, and scholarships. Enjoy a safe work environment with innovative tools, such as a wearable safety badge for nurses. Benefit from additional compensation for night/weekend shifts and higher education. Plus, enjoy malpractice liability insurance and potential loan forgiveness through the New Mexico Higher Education Department.

Type of Opportunity: PRN
FTE: 0.00
Job Exempt: No
Work Shift: Varied Days and Hours (United States of America)

Your Responsibilities:
• Provide direct patient care by assessing, planning, implementing, evaluating, and documenting individual patient needs...
• Coordinate patient care through collaboration with the patient/family and the healthcare team...
• Perform assessments per unit standards and document appropriately...
• Administer medications and treatments as prescribed or according to protocols...
• Identify and support patient and family learning and discharge needs...
• Evaluate patient progression toward outcomes and document effectively...
• Demonstrate competence in clinical emergency situations...
• Delegate tasks to healthcare team members according to their competency...
• Assist with various procedures, treatments, and surgical techniques...
• Support and guide new staff or students as a resource and role model...
• Embrace and incorporate our mission in your caregiving activities...
• Exhibit flexibility by supporting patient care in other departments as needed...
• Assume leadership roles, such as relief charge nurse, as required...
• ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[ICU RN]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/icu-rn-glendale-111.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=111&amp;role=ICU+RN&amp;company=Fusion+Medical+Staffing</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Fusion Medical Staffing]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job #1883812

Glendale, AZ

$1979-2106 /week*

36 hrs /week
• Estimated payments include wages and expense reimbursement, are based on information available to Fusion at time of posting, and could vary depending on factors related to the facility or applicant. Estimated payments do not include taxes, insurance, or other deductions that may occur.

Apply for this job

Job overview

Start date

03/30/2026

Assignment length

13 weeks

Shift

Days

Hours

3 X 12

Facility details

Work setting

Hospital

Number of beds

539

Trauma center

Level II

Charting system

Babyscripts, Buoy Health (Symptom Checker), Cerner (Millennium, PowerChart), Epic, FUJIFILM (Synapse)

Job Details

Fusion Medical Staffing is seeking a ICU RN for a 13-week travel assignment in Glendale, Arizona. As a member of our team, you'll have the opportunity to make a positive impact on the lives of patients while enjoying competitive pay, comprehensive benefits, and the support of a dedicated clinical team.

Required Qualifications:
• One year of recent experience as an ICU RN
• Valid RN license in compliance with state regulations
• Current BLS (AHA/ARC) and ACLS (AHA/ARC) certifications
Preferred Qualifications:
• Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN) certification
• TNCC, NIHSS certification
• Other certifications or licenses may be required for this position
Summary:

The ICU Registered Nurse is responsible for providing comprehensive, critical care to patients in the intensive care unit. This role encompasses assessing and monitoring critically ill patients, operating life-support equipment, administering advanced treatments, and collaborating with multidisciplinary healthcare teams. The position requires strong critical care skills, advanced clinical judgment, excellent communication, and a commitment to maintaining the highest standards of patient safety and professional ethics in high-acuity settings.

Essential Work Functions:
• Assess and monitor critically ill patients, recognizing and r]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse RN Emergency Department - Full-time]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-rn-emergency-department-full-time-queen-creek-110.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=110&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+RN+Emergency+Department+-+Full-time&amp;company=Banner+Health</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Banner Health]]></company>
    <city>Queen Creek</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[**Primary City/State:**

Queen Creek, Arizona
• *Department Name:**

Emergency Ctr-Hosp
• *Work Shift:**

Evening
• *Job Category:**

Nursing

The future is full of possibilities. At Banner Health, we’re excited about what the future holds for health care. That’s why we’re changing the industry to make the experience the best it can be. If you’re ready to change lives, we want to hear from you.
• *Banner Ironwood Medical Center** resides in the heart of San Tan Valley serving Queen Creek, Florence, San Tan Valley, and other neighboring communities. Since opening in 2010, Banner Ironwood Medical Center has provided an excellent patient experience, with all the amenities of a hotel and the highest quality of health care available.  Our thirty-four bed Emergency Department serves both adult and pediatric patients with ACEP board certified physicians capable of managing complex and simple health care emergencies. Patients can count on collaboration and innovation in processes with the use of technologies foundational to Banner’s ability to provide industry leading care.  We hold the State of Arizona designation as a Level IV Trauma Center and the Arizona Chapter American Academy Pediatrics designation as Pediatric Prepared. We have a new twelve bed Pediatric Inpatient Unit and Adult Critical Care Unit offering a healing environment designed to enhance outcomes, healing, and patient safety.

As a **Registered Nurse in our Emergency Department** , you are a vital member of the multi-professional care team, we strive to advance the art and science of patient care, quality, and safety.  If you are looking to work with all patients and a wide range of patient acuity levels, this is the position for you.  **This is a full-time mid shift position working three 12-hour shifts per week from 3:00 PM - 3:30 AM. You will also have the opportunity utilize our self-scheduling tool for shift and weekend coverage. Enjoy an 18%-night shift differential and a flat rate $3/hour weekend sh]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Local Contract Nurse RN - PICU - Pediatric Intensive Care - $66-68 per hour]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/local-contract-nurse-rn-picu-pediatric-intensive-care-66-68-per-hour-mesa-109.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=109&amp;role=Local+Contract+Nurse+RN+-+PICU+-+Pediatric+Intensive+Care+-+$66-68+per+hour&amp;company=LanceSoft</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[LanceSoft]]></company>
    <city>Mesa</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[LanceSoft is seeking a local contract nurse RN PICU - Pediatric Intensive Care for a local contract nursing job in Phoenix, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: PICU - Pediatric Intensive Care
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: 04/06/2026
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours
• Employment Type: Local Contract

Travel RN Opportunity – Pediatric ICU Float Pool 🚨

🏥 Facility: Phoenix Children's Hospital
📍 Location: Phoenix, Arizona

Position: Registered Nurse – Pediatric Critical Care (Float Pool)
🕒 Shift: Night Shift | 3x12s (7:00 PM – 7:30 AM)

Float Units: PICU | CVICU | NICU (Main Campus & Arrowhead Location)

Requirements:
✔ 2+ years Pediatric Critical Care RN experience
✔ AZ RN License or Compact License
✔ BLS, PALS, and NRP (AHA)
✔ Children’s hospital experience preferred

📌 Schedule: Every other weekend required

About LanceSoft

Established in 2000, LanceSoft is a Certified MBE and Woman-Owned organization. Lancesoft Inc. is one of the highest rated companies in the industry. We have been recognized as one of the Largest Staffing firms and ranked in the top 50 fastest Growing Healthcare Staffing firms in 2022. Lancesoft offers short- and long-term contracts, permanent placements, and travel opportunities to credentialed and experienced professionals throughout the United States. We pride ourselves on having industry leading benefits. We understand the importance of partnering with an expert who values your needs, which is why we’re 100% committed to finding you an assignment that best matches your career and lifestyle goals. Our team of experienced career specialists takes the time to understand your needs and match you with the right job Lancesoft has been chosen by Staffing Industry Analysts as one of the Best Staffing Firms to Work for.LanceSoft specializes in providing Registered Nurses, Nurse Practitioners, LPNs/LVNs, Social Workers, Medical Assistants, and Certified Nursing Assistants to work in Acute Care Centers, Skille]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>contractor</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Cardiac Recovery Unit]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-cardiac-recovery-unit-sun-city-108.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=108&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Cardiac+Recovery+Unit&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

1100 Central Avenue SE Albuquerque, NM 87106-4930

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Summary:

Join our dedicated team at Presbyterian as an RN in the Cardiac Recovery Unit, where the care you provide matters. We are excited to welcome both new graduates and seasoned RNs! New graduates can take advantage of our comprehensive residency program, including monthly seminars, peer support sessions, and mentorship opportunities. This program is specifically designed to foster your growth and transition into practice.

Here, your growth and well-being are our priorities.
Enjoy numerous educational and career development options, such as tuition and certification reimbursement, scholarship opportunities, and staff safety measures that enhance your work environment. Also available are differentials for night/weekend shifts, higher education, and certifications, along with malpractice liability insurance. Benefit from loan forgiveness options through the New Mexico Higher Education Department and utilize our EPIC electronic charting system.

Type of Opportunity: Full time FTE: 0.90 Job Exempt: No Work Shift: 12 Hour Nights (United States of America)

Responsibilities:

The Cardiac Recovery Unit is a 38-bed unit dedicated to providing the highest level of patient care for those requiring telemetry monitoring due to cardiovascular issues such as cardiac arrhythmias and heart failure. Our team cares for patients recovering from myocardial infarctions, coronary procedures, pacemaker placements, and electrophysiology interventions. With approximately 50% of our patients needing progressive care, we deliver quality care through a collaborative approach and create personalized discharge plans to meet outpatient needs.

Sign-on and relocation bonuses are available for qualified candidates.

Qualifications:
• Minimum Associate Degree: Degree from an accredited academic nursing program preferred
• Credentials: Registered Nurse-NM, St]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Case Manager Inpatient - RN - ED/OBS/ACH]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-case-manager-inpatient-rn-edobsach-avondale-107.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=107&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Case+Manager+Inpatient+-+RN+-+ED/OBS/ACH&amp;company=Mayo+Clinic</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Mayo Clinic]]></company>
    <city>Avondale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Why Mayo Clinic

Mayo Clinic is top-ranked in more specialties than any other care provider according to U.S. News & World Report. As we work together to put the needs of the patient first, we are also dedicated to our employees, investing in competitive compensation and comprehensive benefit plans – to take care of you and your family, now and in the future. And with continuing education and advancement opportunities at every turn, you can build a long, successful career with Mayo Clinic.

Benefits Highlights
• Medical: Multiple plan options.
• Dental: Delta Dental or reimbursement account for flexible coverage.
• Vision: Affordable plan with national network.
• Pre-Tax Savings: HSA and FSAs for eligible expenses.
• Retirement: Competitive retirement package to secure your future.

Responsibilities

The Registered Nurse (RN) Case Manager works within an interdisciplinary team to facilitate the patient plan of care throughout the continuum of care by ensuring appropriate utilization management, care coordination, resource utilization, and clinical documentation. The RN Case Manager will function within the Mayo Clinical Nursing Professional Practice Model, which includes accountability for assessing, planning, implementing, evaluating, and communicating the patient care plan progression. The RN Case Manager utilizes the principles of mutual respect, patient/family advocacy and provides leadership within the team of internal partners and outside agencies to facilitate best practices that achieve quality clinical, financial, and patient satisfaction outcomes. The RN Case Manager provides leadership through education on case management/utilization management concepts, committee work, research, and community involvement. The RN Case Manager bridges communication between providers, patients and families, members of the interdisciplinary team, and outside agencies to assure high-quality care that meets the patient's needs and is delivered in a cost-effective and timely ma]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse - RN - Cardiac Cath Lab - Competitive Weekly Pay]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-cardiac-cath-lab-competitive-weekly-pay-glendale-106.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=106&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+-+RN+-+Cardiac+Cath+Lab+-+Competitive+Weekly+Pay&amp;company=Host+Healthcare</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Host Healthcare]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Host Healthcare is seeking an experienced Cardiac Cath Lab Registered Nurse for an exciting Travel Nursing job in Glendale, AZ. Shift: Inquire Start Date: 03/30/2026 Duration: 13 weeks Pay: $2136.6 / Week
About Host Healthcare:

At Host Healthcare, we are dedicated to empowering the life and healthcare career you deserve. As a nurse, allied, or therapy professional, you will be matched to one of our responsive recruiters who will have your back throughout your journey. You will also be connected with a full support team that was rated #1 in Nursing Satisfaction by MIT Sloan Management Review.

No matter if you want to explore the other side of the country or stay close to home, our team can help you get there. With Host Healthcare, you'll get exclusive access to thousands of jobs in all 50 states. This means you get priority access to apply to travel and local assignments before other applicants.

We know that you are so much more than a number and we work hard to ensure you have the best benefits for you and your loved ones. During your assignment, you'll be able to select premium benefits like Day-1 health coverage, 401K matching, travel reimbursements, housing support and more.

Take control of your life and career with Host Healthcare.

Benefits:
• A dedicated and responsive recruiter who has your back
• Priority access to jobs in all 50 states at every major healthcare system
• Day-1 medical benefits that last up to 30 days between assignments
• Day-1 401K with company matching after 6 months
• 24/7 support
• Clinical support throughout your assignment]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[$1,727 per week for Travel Nurse RN - Telemetry in Chandler, AZ]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/1727-per-week-for-travel-nurse-rn-telemetry-in-chandler-az-chandler-105.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=105&amp;role=$1,727+per+week+for+Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Telemetry+in+Chandler,+AZ&amp;company=GQR+Healthcare</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[GQR Healthcare]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Start Date: ASAP

Shift: 3x12

GQR Healthcare is representing a well-known health system seeking experienced Telemetry providers to add to their team. If you are passionate about providing exceptional care and looking to explore a rewarding career opportunity, we'd love to hear from you!

Apply now, and a dedicated GQR consultant will connect with you to discuss the role, answer your questions, and guide you through the process.

About GQR Healthcare:

At GQR Healthcare, we are committed to supporting healthcare professionals at every stage of their careers. When you partner with us, you gain access to a wide range of benefits and support, including:
• Day 1 Benefits: Enjoy comprehensive healthcare coverage, including medical, dental, and vision plans, starting on your first day.
• Guaranteed Hours: We provide contract stability by offering guaranteed hours, ensuring you have the predictability you need.
• Continuing Education & Development: We invest in your growth by offering opportunities for professional development and ongoing education.
• 24/7 Consultant Support: Our dedicated consultants are available around the clock to assist with any needs or questions you have.
• Seamless Placement Process: We handle all the details, from onboarding to interviews, so you can focus on what you do best - providing exceptional patient care.

Partnering with GQR means more than just finding your next job - it's about building a meaningful career with a team that truly supports your goals.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>contractor</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - Telemetry - $2,027 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-telemetry-2027-per-week-chandler-104.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=104&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Telemetry+-+$2,027+per+week&amp;company=AMN+Healthcare+Nursing</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[AMN Healthcare Nursing]]></company>
    <city>Chandler</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[AMN Healthcare Nursing is seeking a travel nurse RN Telemetry for a travel nursing job in CHANDLER, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: Telemetry
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: ASAP
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, nights
• Employment Type: Travel

Job Description & Requirements

Registered Nurse – Telemetry - Travel - (Tele RN)

StartDate: 2/23/2026
Available Shifts: 12 N
Pay Rate: $1966.00 - $2088.00

Since 1961, Dignity Health Chandler Regional Medical Center has been at the heart of the health and well-being of our community.

Its humble beginnings as a true community hospital, which opened with only 40 beds, 25 employees and 91 volunteers, laid the foundation for the full-service, acute-care hospital it has become.

Today, Chandler Regional is a 429-bed, non-profit hospital with more than 2,600 employees, and more than 1,100 doctors on staff representing all major specialties.

Required Qualifications
Registered Nurse, Telemetry
Experience: 2 years
Licenses: RN(Compact Accepted)(Copy needed)
Certifications: ACLS(Copy Needed); BLS(Copy Needed); CERT-NIH Stroke Scale(Copy Needed)
SSN Required
DOB Required
References: 2 References in entire work history

ACLS
BLS
NIHSS

Facility Location

Job Benefits

At AMN Healthcare we take care of our travelers! We offer:
• Competitive pay rates
• Free, quality, private housing
• Medical, Dental, Vision
• 401(k) and Flex Spending
• Life Insurance
• Accident and Short-term Disability Coverage
• Free Continuing Education
• Refer a friend and earn extra cash!

About the Company

At AMN Healthcare, we strive to be recognized as the most trusted, innovative, and influential force in helping healthcare organizations provide quality patient care that continually evolves to make healthcare more human, more effective, and more achievable.

Telemetry nurse, telemetry, nurse, nursing, RN, R.N., registered nurse, hospital, medical, healthcare, health care, patient care, tele RN

American Mobile]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - PCU - Progressive Care Unit - $2,441 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-pcu-progressive-care-unit-2441-per-week-sun-city-west-103.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=103&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+PCU+-+Progressive+Care+Unit+-+$2,441+per+week&amp;company=Advantis+Medical+Staffing</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Advantis Medical Staffing]]></company>
    <city>Sun City West</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Advantis Medical is seeking a travel nurse RN PCU - Progressive Care Unit for a travel nursing job in Sun City West, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: PCU - Progressive Care Unit
• Discipline: RN
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, nights
• Employment Type: Travel

Advantis Medical, the #1 rated travel nurse agency, is currently seeking an experienced PCU Registered Nurse (RN) for an exciting new travel job in Sun City West, AZ 85375. This rewarding travel job offers a contract duration of 13 weeks and a Night shift. With us, you'll enjoy a superior pay and benefits package starting on day 1, along with our personalized service where we set the gold standard in clinician care. As a Joint-Commission-certified agency, we promise a seamless and stress-free experience. As a PCU travel nurse, you will provide compassionate and high-quality care to patients ensuring their well-being and recovery.

Job Details

Facility: Banner - Del Webb Medical Center

Location: Sun City West, AZ 85375

Contract Length: 13 Weeks

Shift: Nights

Start Date: ASAP

Qualifications

• 2 years of PCU staff experience or equivalent

• BSN Degree or Associate of Science in Nursing

• Current nursing license

• A valid State Issued Driver's License or State ID

If you are an experienced PCU Registered Nurse (RN) with a passion for providing exceptional patient care, just let us know you’re interested. We'll get you started on your next travel nurse adventure in Sun City West, AZ 85375.

Advantis Medical Job ID #609490. Pay package is based on 12 hour shifts and 36 hours per week (subject to confirmation) with tax-free stipend amount to be determined.
About Advantis Medical

Advantis Medical Staffing is ranked #1 by travel clinicians because of our relentless focus on matching our travel clinicians with their next dream assignment. We accomplish this by making significant investments in technology and have married it with an exceptional human experience f]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Up to $38,000 Sign-on Bonus]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-up-to-38000-sign-on-bonus-new-river-102.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=102&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Up+to+$38,000+Sign-on+Bonus&amp;company=Federal+Bureau+of+Prisons</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Federal Bureau of Prisons]]></company>
    <city>New River</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Summary
Corrections professionals who foster a humane and secure environment and ensure public safety by preparing individuals for successful reentry into our communities.

Duties

Registered Nurse provides direct patient care services in accordance with legal, ethical and institution standards. Provides nursing care of a general nature to inmates in the institution hospital/clinic, and may be provided to patients in specific areas, e.g., psychiatric, operating room, orthopedics, geriatrics, etc. Develops a nursing assessment for each patient, to include planning, implementing, and evaluating nursing care. May assess and identify high risk symptoms/behaviors in patients, to include suicidal risk, homicidal risk and risk for verbal and/or physical abuse. Completes nutritional screening as part of the assessment and refers patient to a dietitian for a nutritional assessment if necessary. Monitors, evaluates and revises the plan of care as needed. May also assess and document the discharge planning needs of a patient. Delegates and coordinates care based on assessments. Along with all other correctional institution employees, incumbent is charged with responsibility for maintaining security of the institution. The staff correctional responsibilities precede all others required by this position and is performed on a regular and recurring basis.]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse RN Observation Unit Registry - Full-time]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-rn-observation-unit-registry-full-time-apache-junction-101.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=101&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+RN+Observation+Unit+Registry+-+Full-time&amp;company=Banner+Health</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Banner Health]]></company>
    <city>Apache Junction</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[**Primary City/State:**

Mesa, Arizona
• *Department Name:**

Banner Staffing Services-AZ
• *Work Shift:**

Varied
• *Job Category:**

Nursing

Flexible scheduling. Rewarding careers. Nurses are the heartbeat of a hospital, and we do our best to keep our nurses’ hearts beating happily and well. Part of this is the breadth of career options for nurses with Banner Staffing Services. Apply today.

This is an excellent opportunity to join Banner Health. As an RN for _Banner Staffing Services_ you will self-schedule a minimum of 2 shifts per month with no weekend commitment. There are opportunities for both Day and Night shift as well as to pick up shifts at other Banner Health locations.

You must have Acute Care Registered Nurse work experience for a minimum of 12 months within the last year and a half. BLS & ACLS are required upon hire.
• *Banner Staffing Services (BSS) offers Registry/Per Diem opportunities within Banner Health.** Registry/Per Diem positions are utilized as needed within our facilities. These positions offer flexibility in scheduling and are great way to start your career with Banner Health. As a BSS team member, you are eligible to apply (at any time) as an internal applicant to any regular opportunities within Banner Health.

Banner Staffing Services is also excited to provide **Banner Bedside Commitment** opportunities (Formally Banner Travel). Banner Staffing Employees can pick up 8, 10, or 13 week commitments at a wide variety of Banner Facilities in the following state: Wyoming, Nevada, Nebraska, California, Arizona and Colorado
• *As a valued and respected Banner Health team member, you will enjoy:**

• Competitive wages

• Paid orientation

• Flexible Schedules (select positions)

• Fewer Shifts Cancelled

• Weekly pay

• 403(b) Pre-tax retirement

• Employee Assistance Program

• Employee wellness program

• Discount Entertainment tickets

• Restaurant/Shopping discounts

• Auto Purchase Plan
• *Registry/Per Diem positions do not have guaran]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - General Medical Unit with $17,500 Sign-On Bonus]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-general-medical-unit-with-17500-sign-on-bonus-sun-city-100.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=100&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+General+Medical+Unit+with+$17,500+Sign-On+Bonus&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

2100 N Dr Martin Luther King Jr Blvd Clovis, NM 88101-9412

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Summary:

Join our dedicated team at Presbyterian Healthcare Services as a skilled Registered Nurse in the General Medical Unit. This is an excellent opportunity to build your career while making a meaningful difference in the lives of patients.

Why Choose Us?
• Access to educational and career development options, including tuition reimbursement and scholarship opportunities.
• Staff Safety initiative with wearable badges for quick access to help when needed.
• Differentials offered for night/weekend shifts, higher education, certifications, and eligible lead roles.
• Comprehensive malpractice liability insurance coverage.
• Loan forgiveness programs available through the New Mexico Higher Education Department.
• Experience working with the EPIC electronic charting system.

Type of Opportunity: Full time | FTE: 0.90 | Job Exempt: No | Work Shift: Varied Days and Hours

Responsibilities:

As a Registered Nurse, you will be responsible for:
• Providing primary nursing care and coordinating care for assigned patients of all ages.
• Developing individualized care plans in consultation with the physician, tailored to the patient's specific needs.

Qualifications:
• Current State of New Mexico or Compact State Nursing License or Graduate Nurse Permit required.
• Degree from an accredited academic nursing program (conditional programs may be considered with approval).

Your Well-Being Matters:

At Presbyterian, we prioritize your well-being with a fun and engaging wellness program that includes:
• Free on-site and community-based gyms.
• Nutrition coaching and classes.
• Resources for mindfulness and meditation.
• Wellness challenges to encourage healthy living.

About Presbyterian Healthcare Services:

Since 1908, Presbyterian has been committed to improving the health of our patients, members, and communities. As New Mexico']]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse Med Surg Float Pool]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-med-surg-float-pool-phoenix-99.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=99&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+Med+Surg+Float+Pool&amp;company=Intermountain+Health</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Health]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Job Description:

The Registered Nurse (RN) is a professional caregiver who assumes responsibility and accountability for assessing, planning, implementing and evaluating care of patients.

The staff RN utilizes the nursing process by use of technology, therapeutic intervention, evidence-based practice and coordination of care with other health team members.

Job SummaryAs a Float Registered Nurse on our Medical Surgical Floors, you will bring your full self—body, mind, heart, and spirit—to your work.

You will provide care across various departments, including Med Surg, Ortho Medical Trauma, Medical Oncology Palliative Care, Observation, and Neuro Surgical Trauma.
Your compassionate nature and strong integrity will resonate with patients and colleagues alike.
About UsSt.

Vincent Hospital, a286-bed Level I Trauma Center, has been a cornerstone of healthcare in Montana and the surrounding area since 1898.

We are proud to have achieved:

Magnet Recognition:
The nation's highest honor for nursing excellence.
Healthgrades Hospital Quality &

Specialty Clinical Quality Awards:
Surgical Care Excellence Award for 2025

Outstanding Patient Experience Award for 2024 and 2023Additionally, our facility is recognized as a Comprehensive Stroke Center, a Platinum Level Comprehensive Chest Pain Center, a Certified Cancer Center, a Level 3 NICU, and a Comprehensive Maternal-Fetal Medicine program.
Key ResponsibilitiesAs a Float Medical Surgical Registered Nurse, you will need to:

Adapt calmly and effectively to rapidly changing situations.
Collaborate as part of a team with physicians and peers.
Thrive in a fast-paced environment.
Prioritize quality care with patients' best interests at heart.
Adhere to procedural and documentation standards.
Oversee care provided by CNAs.
Follow hospital, regulatory, and professional guidelines, policies, and procedures.
Communicate with professionalism, compassion, and effectiveness.
Position Details

Shift:
FULL TIME and PART TIME

Locations:]]></description>
    <salary>65000-115000</salary>
    <jobtype>full-time and part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - Med Surg / Telemetry - $1,873 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-med-surg-telemetry-1873-per-week-peoria-98.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=98&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Med+Surg+/+Telemetry+-+$1,873+per+week&amp;company=Trustaff</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Trustaff]]></company>
    <city>Peoria</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Trustaff is seeking a travel nurse RN Med Surg / Telemetry for a travel nursing job in Peoria, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: Med Surg / Telemetry
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: 03/20/2026
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, nights
• Employment Type: Travel

As a MS/Telemetry RN, you'll provide care for adult patients experiencing general medical conditions or general surgical procedures that require hospitalization and intervention. MS/Tele RNs closely monitor the patients' condition, including heart function, so you must be able to accurately review telemetry readouts.

Trustaff Job ID #993564. Pay package is based on 12 hour shifts and 36 hours per week (subject to confirmation) with tax-free stipend amount to be determined. Posted job title: M/S Tele
About Trustaff

Our nurse-first attitude has set us apart from other travel nursing agencies

When you join the Trustaff family, you’re more than just a body filling a role—you're a vibrant individual with dreams and aspirations. As one of the nation's leading travel nursing companies, your recruiter will work with you one-on-one to guide your career and help you achieve your goals.
• You decide when and where you want to work
• Enjoy industry-leading pay, benefits, and bonuses
• Experience new people and places
• Grow your clinical skills and expand your experience

Travel nursing lets you take your professional career to the next level while maintaining your flexibility and freedom. At Trustaff, we put you first, so you never have to compromise your work or pay. We are proud to have one of the highest nurse retention rates in the country. Some of the other reasons people choose us include:
• Priority access to thousands of travel nursing jobs
• Industry-leading pay
• Guaranteed weekly hours
• Experienced recruiters
• Comprehensive benefits, including medical, dental, and vision
• 401k with employer match
• Assistance with travel, compliance, and housing
• Great bonuses]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Inpatient Surgical Registered Nurse]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/inpatient-surgical-registered-nurse-paradise-valley-97.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=97&amp;role=Inpatient+Surgical+Registered+Nurse&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Paradise Valley</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

301 E Miel de Luna Tucumcari, NM 88401-3810

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Summary:

Join a dedicated team as a Registered Nurse in Inpatient Surgical Nursing, where you'll utilize your nursing skills to provide exceptional care to patients. You will assess, plan, implement, and evaluate patient care in a supportive and collaborative environment.

How you grow, learn and thrive matters here.
At our organization, we prioritize your development with educational and career growth options, including:
• Tuition and certification reimbursement
• Scholarship opportunities
• Safety tools for staff
• Shift differentials for night/weekend shifts and higher education
• Malpractice liability insurance
• Loan forgiveness options through the New Mexico Higher Education Department
• EPIC electronic charting system

Type of Opportunity: Part-time
FTE: 0.60
Work Shift: 12 Hour Nights
Job Exempt: No

Responsibilities:
• Deliver direct patient care by assessing, planning, implementing, and evaluating individual patient needs.
• Coordinate patient care in collaboration with patients, families, and healthcare teams.
• Perform comprehensive assessments and accurately document patient data.
• Administer medications and treatments as prescribed, following established protocols.
• Identify and address patient and family educational needs throughout the care process.
• Manage emergency situations with confidence.
• Delegate appropriate tasks to team members based on their competency.
• Provide guidance and supervision to LPNs and non-licensed personnel.
• Support orientation for new staff and students, serving as a professional role model.
• Participate in governance and quality improvement activities on the unit.

Qualifications:
• Current New Mexico or Compact State Nursing License or Graduate Nurse Permit required.
• Degree from an accredited academic nursing program; minimum ADN required, with a commitment to complete BSN within 5 ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - Rehabilitation - $1,795 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-rehabilitation-1795-per-week-peoria-96.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=96&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Rehabilitation+-+$1,795+per+week&amp;company=Triage+Staffing+|+Healthcare+Staffing</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Triage Staffing | Healthcare Staffing]]></company>
    <city>Peoria</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Triage Staffing is seeking a travel nurse RN Rehabilitation for a travel nursing job in Peoria, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: Rehabilitation
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: 03/21/2026
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, nights
• Employment Type: Travel

Travel Nursing: Rehabilitation Peoria
Location: Peoria
Start Date: 3/21/2026
Shift Details: 12H Nights
36 hours per week
Length: 13 WEEKS

Apply for specific facility details.Rehab RN

Triage Staffing Job ID #JVDF7Y46. Posted job title: Nursing: Rehabilitation
About Triage Staffing

At Triage, we prefer to be real. Real about expectations—both ours and yours. Real about how a decision you make today could affect your tomorrows. Real about how compensation actually works. Real about how great—or grating—your next supervisor may be.

Being real allows everyone at Triage to be ready. Ready to serve you with real honesty. So if that gig near the ocean is really no day at the beach, or that third shift comes with a second-class rate, we tell you. So you can be ready, too.

We staff all five major divisions of acute care—nursing, lab, radiology, cardiopulmonary and rehab therapy, offering:

- Competitive, custom pay packages

- One point of contact for both travelers and facilities (per division)

- A reliable recruiter who's got your back throughout your entire assignment

- In-house compliance and accounting specialists

- A clinical liaison team available 24/7 to offer medical and professional support and career development

- A mentoring program that is run and managed by actual clinicians—yeah, you read that right

- And more (because of course there’s more)

Are we the biggest? No. Are we the best? That’s rather subjective, but we’re trying to be. Will we work like hell to get you as close to your idea of heaven as possible? Yes. Yes, we will.

Benefits:
• Day One comprehensive, nationwide insurance plans for health, vision and dental and life—including a HSA option
• Day]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Part-time Registered Nurse]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/part-time-registered-nurse-scottsdale-95.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=95&amp;role=Part-time+Registered+Nurse&amp;company=The+Terraces+of+Phoenix+-+a+HumanGood+community</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[The Terraces of Phoenix - a HumanGood community]]></company>
    <city>Scottsdale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[The Terraces of Phoenix, a HumanGood life plan community, is seeking a dedicated and experienced Part-time Registered Nurse (RN) to join our Skilled Nursing Team.
• * Part-time, 24 hours/week ** Work every other Weekend ** 2pm - 10pm ** $42 - $53/Hr. (DOE)

As a Registered Nurse (RN), you will play a crucial role in addressing the nursing needs of our residents, while actively embracing our Philosophy for person-directed Care. You will contribute to fostering a safe and healthy environment for residents, staff, and visitors, allowing everyone to engage meaningfully in daily life.

To thrive in this role, you should possess:
• Current RN license in the relevant state
• Current CPR certification
• 1-2 years of recent or prior experience in skilled nursing
• Background in post-acute, sub-acute, or senior care nursing

What’s in it for you?

Joining HumanGood means being part of a larger mission focused on enhancing the lives of our residents. We are more than just a workplace; we are committed to empowering everyone we serve to reach their fullest potential. This starts with YOU.

We offer an impressive package of benefits for our part-time and full-time Team Members that can enhance your overall compensation by up to 40% of your base pay.

For Full-Time Team Members:
• 20 days of paid time off (grows with service) plus 7 company-paid holidays
• 401(k) plan with up to 4% employer match and immediate vesting
• Health, Dental, and Vision Plans beginning the 1st of the month after your start date
• $25 + Tax per line for a Cell Phone Plan
• Tuition Reimbursement
• Comprehensive employer-paid employee assistance program

For Part-Time/Per Diem Team Members:
• Medical benefits start the 1st of the month following your start date
• Matching 401(k)
• $25 + Tax per line for a Cell Phone Plan

Join us at HumanGood and discover the difference we can make together!

Equal Opportunity Employer. This employer is required to notify all applicants of their rights pursuant to federal ]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>part-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[RN Registered Nurse Looking for an RN to join our growing team!]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/rn-registered-nurse-looking-for-an-rn-to-join-our-growing-team-paradise-valley-9.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=94&amp;role=RN+Registered+Nurse+Looking+for+an+RN+to+join+our+growing+team!&amp;company=Life+Care+Center+of+Paradise+Valley+AZ</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Life Care Center of Paradise Valley AZ]]></company>
    <city>Paradise Valley</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Life Care Center of Paradise Valley is seeking compassionate and dedicated Registered Nurses to join our growing team!

We offer:
• Competitive pay
• 401 (k) with employer match
• Above -indurstry staffing levels
• Strong, supportive Nurse Management team
• Opportunities for growth and advancement

Whether you're a new graduate or an experiences nurse ready for a positive change, we would love to have you join our team.

Join a facility where leadership supports you, teamwork is valued and quality of care if our priority.

Apply today and grow with us!

Come and grow with us! We are affiliated with Life Care Centers of America, which is a privately owned 47-year industry leader in healthcare with more than 200 locations across the U.S. We are currently seeking a qualified Registered Nurse to add to our team of professionals. We believe that every job in our company plays a vital role in our continued growth and commitment to provide quality patient care. We believe in providing our associates with opportunities to help them reach their maximum potential through working with strong multidisciplinary teams. We invites you to come and join our growing team.

As an important member of our interdisciplinary team, the RN delivers quality nursing care to patients through interpersonal contact and provides care and services to allow patients to attain or maintain the highest practicable physical, mental, and psychosocial well-being in accordance with all applicable laws, regulations, and Life Care standards. Your role includes evaluating patient needs through ongoing assessment and revise care plans based on changes in the patient’s condition. On a daily basis you must be able to provide clinical supervision to C N As and LPNs.
Education, Experience, and Licensure Requirements
• Nursing diploma (associate’s or bachelor’s degree in nursing)
• Currently licensed/registered in applicable State. Must maintain an active Registered Nurse (RN) license in good standing throughout e]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel CVICU/ICU Registered Nurse - $2,335 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-cvicuicu-registered-nurse-2335-per-week-sun-city-93.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=93&amp;role=Travel+CVICU/ICU+Registered+Nurse+-+$2,335+per+week&amp;company=HCS+247+Travel</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[HCS 247 Travel]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[HCS 247 Travel is seeking a travel nurse RN CVICU for a travel nursing job in Sun City, Arizona.Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: CVICU
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: 03/30/2026
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, days
• Employment Type: Travel

HCS 247 Travel Job ID #62364381. Pay package is based on 12 hour shifts and 36 hours per week (subject to confirmation) with tax-free stipend amount to be determined.About HCS 247 Travel

HCS 24/7 is a national healthcare staffing organization specializing in the placement of Registered Nurses and Allied health professionals across acute care and other clinical settings. We support travel assignments, local short- and long-term contracts, per diem, temp-to-perm, and direct hire opportunities nationwide.

Our clinical coverage includes Registered Nurse specialties such as ER, ICU, Med-Surg, Telemetry, Step-Down, OR, PACU, L&D, Mother/Baby, NICU, Cath Lab, Endoscopy, and more along with a full range of allied and imaging professionals, including Respiratory Therapists, Surgical Technicians, X-Ray Techs, CT Techs, MRI Techs, Interventional Radiology (IR) Techs, Cath Lab Techs, Ultrasound/Sonographers, Mammography Techs, and Nuclear Medicine Techs.

With competitive compensation and benefits, consistent opportunities, and a clinician-first approach backed by top-rated customer service, HCS 24/7 delivers a seamless experience from initial application through assignment completion.

Benefits
• Holiday Pay
• Guaranteed Hours
• Continuing Education
• Mileage reimbursement
• Referral bonus
• Medical benefits
• Dental benefits
• Vision benefits
• License and certification reimbursement
• Life insurance
• Benefits start day 1
• Weekly pay]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - Long Term Acute Care - $2,033 per week]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-long-term-acute-care-2033-per-week-sun-city-92.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=92&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Long+Term+Acute+Care+-+$2,033+per+week&amp;company=Focus+Staff</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Focus Staff]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Focus Staff is seeking a travel nurse RN Long Term Acute Care for a travel nursing job in Sun City, Arizona.
Job Description & Requirements
• Specialty: Long Term Acute Care
• Discipline: RN
• Start Date: 03/23/2026
• Duration: 13 weeks
• 36 hours per week
• Shift: 12 hours, nights
• Employment Type: Travel

Focus Staff is seeking a Long Term Acute Care Registered Nurse for a travel contract in Sun City, AZ. The ideal candidate will have at least 1 year of experience in a LTAC setting.

Contract Length: 13 Weeks

Start Date: 03/23/2026

Shift: 3x12 Nights

Benefits for Travel LTAC RNs:
• Health insurance
• Vision insurance
• Dental insurance
• Life insurance
• Licensure reimbursement
• Travel reimbursement
• Relocation assistance
• 401(k)
• 401(k) matching
• Competitive pay
• Referral bonus
• Holiday bonus

Requirements:
• 1 Year of Experience, 2 Preferred
• Valid AZ RN License
• BLS (Basic Life Support)
• ACLS
• Eligible to work in the United States

About Focus Staff:

Focus Staff is a traveler-first nurse and healthcare staffing agency! We prioritize the needs of our travelers, giving you complete control over your journey. Our mission is to help you create the life you love, explore the country and do what you do best, help others.

Interested in becoming a traveler with Focus Staff? Discover why travelers choose us, apply today!

All-Star Status:
• Dallas 100 (Multiple Years in a Row)
• Inc. 5000
• Middle Market 50
• Certified by The Joint Commission
• Best of Staffing Talent Satisfaction 2022
• Best of Staffing Client Satisfaction 2022
• Fastest-Growing US Staffing Firms 2017

If you’re seeking a Travel Long Term Acute Care Nurse position in Sun City, AZ and are looking to work with an agency that will listen to your needs and career goals, then Focus Staff is the right place to be. We are proud of our ability to build relationships with all our healthcare professionals, whether you’re seeking travel assignments, PR or permanent positions.

We Offer:
• Immedia]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - General Medical Unit - $17,500 Sign-On Bonus - Day Shift]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-general-medical-unit-17500-sign-on-bonus-day-shift-sun-city-91.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=91&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+General+Medical+Unit+-+$17,500+Sign-On+Bonus+-+Day+Shift&amp;company=Presbyterian+Healthcare+Services</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Presbyterian Healthcare Services]]></company>
    <city>Sun City</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Location Address:

2100 N Dr Martin Luther King Jr Blvd Clovis, NM 88101-9412

Compensation Pay Range:

Minimum Offer $37.80 Maximum Offer $51.00

Join Our Team!
Presbyterian Healthcare Services is seeking a dedicated Registered Nurse (RN) to make a meaningful impact on patient care in our General Medical Unit. Enjoy a supportive work environment where your professional growth is a priority.

Your Growth Matters:
We provide numerous opportunities for educational and career development, including:
• Tuition and certification reimbursement
• Scholarship opportunities
• Access to a wearable badge for staff safety
• Shift differentials for nights/weekends and additional incentives for higher education and certifications
• Malpractice liability insurance.
• Loan forgiveness opportunities through the New Mexico Higher Education Department
• Use of EPIC electronic charting system.

Job Type: Full-time, FTE: 0.90
Work Shift: 12 Hour Days (United States of America)

Key Responsibilities:
Your primary role will include:
• Utilizing the nursing process to deliver direct patient care to an assigned group of patients during your shift
• Prioritizing nursing care effectively, optimizing time and resources while adhering to established standards.

Qualifications:
To be successful in this role, you must possess:
• A valid State of New Mexico or Compact State Nursing License or Graduate Nurse Permit
• A degree from an accredited academic nursing program (conditional programs may require approval by system CNO).

Your Well-Being is Our Priority:
Enjoy a comprehensive wellness program that includes:
• Free on-site and community-based gyms
• Nutrition coaching and classes
• Mindfulness and meditation resources
• Engaging wellness challenges.

About Presbyterian Healthcare Services:
Presbyterian is committed to enhancing the health of patients, members, and the communities we serve. As New Mexico's largest private employer, our network includes nine hospitals and a multi-specialty medic]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN), Behavioral Health]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-rn-behavioral-health-glendale-90.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=90&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+(RN),+Behavioral+Health&amp;company=Copper+Springs</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Copper Springs]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Description

Full Time RN

Day Shift

3x12

Your experience matters

At Copper Springs, Behavioral Health Hospital, we are driven by a profound commitment to prioritize your well-being so you can provide exceptional care to others. Here, you're not just valued as an employee, but as a person. As a Registered Nurse (RN) joining our team, you're embracing a vital mission dedicated to making communities healthier. Join us on this meaningful journey where your skills, compassion, and dedication will make a remarkable difference in the lives of those we serve.

More about our team

We provide evidence-based, transformational care for a broad range of mental health and addiction concerns in a compassionate, comfortable environment.

How you'll contribute
• Support the organization, program and unit philosophy of care
• Coordinate and deliver quality general and psychiatric nursing care to patients
• Ensure medical Orders are followed, initiate and follow treatment planning
• Act as a patient advocate at all times

Why join us

We believe that investing in our employees is the first step to providing excellent patient care. In addition to your base compensation, this position also offers:
• Comprehensive Benefits: Multiple levels of medical, dental and vision coverage for full-time and part-time employees.
• Financial Protection & PTO: Life, accident, critical illness, hospital indemnity insurance, short- and long-term disability, paid family leave and paid time off.
• Financial & Career Growth: Higher education and certification tuition assistance, loan assistance and 401(k) retirement package and company match.
• Employee Well-being: Mental, physical, and financial wellness programs (free gym memberships, virtual care appointments, mental health services and discount programs).
• Professional Development: Ongoing learning and career advancement opportunities.

What we're looking for
• Graduate from an accredited program of professional nursing training
• Current unencumb]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse RN PreOp PACU PRN - Full-time]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-rn-preop-pacu-prn-full-time-glendale-89.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=89&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+RN+PreOp+PACU+PRN+-+Full-time&amp;company=Banner+Health</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Banner Health]]></company>
    <city>Glendale</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[**Primary City/State:**

Mesa, Arizona
• *Department Name:**

Banner Staffing Services-AZ
• *Work Shift:**

Day
• *Job Category:**

Nursing

A rewarding career that fits your life. Banner Staffing Services offers a world of opportunities to make an impact on one of the country’s leading health systems. If you’re looking to leverage your abilities – you belong at Banner Staffing Services.
• **Preferred candidates for this position will have prior RN PreOp/PACU experience.**
• *Banner Staffing Services (BSS) offers Registry/Per Diem** opportunities within Banner Health. Registry/Per Diem positions are utilized as needed within our facilities. These positions are great way to start your career with Banner Health. As a BSS team member, you are eligible to apply (at any time) as an internal applicant to any regular opportunities within Banner Health.
• *As a valued and respected Banner Health team member, you will enjoy:**

Competitive wages

Paid orientation

Flexible Schedules (select positions)

Fewer Shifts Cancelled

Weekly pay

403(b) Pre-tax retirement

Resources for living (Employee Assistance Program)

MyWell-Being (Wellness program)

Discount Entertainment tickets

Restaurant/Shopping discounts
• *Registry/Per Diem positions do not have guaranteed hours and no medical benefits package is offered.** Completion of post-offer Occupational Health physical assessment, drug screen and background check (includes; employment, criminal and education) is required.

POSITION SUMMARY

This position assesses, plans, implements, evaluates and documents nursing care of patients in accordance with organizational policies and in accordance with standards of professional nursing practice utilizing the framework for professional nursing practice and development. This position is accountable for the quality of nursing services delivered by self or others who are under their direction. This position utilizes specialized knowledge, judgment, and nursing skills necessary to assess da]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Travel Nurse RN - Intermediate Care]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/travel-nurse-rn-intermediate-care-phoenix-88.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=88&amp;role=Travel+Nurse+RN+-+Intermediate+Care&amp;company=TravelNurseSource</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[TravelNurseSource]]></company>
    <city>Phoenix</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) | Intermediate Care Location: Lake Havasu City, AZ Agency: GLC Group, GLC On-The-Go Pay: Competitive weekly pay (inquire for details) Shift Information: Nights - 3 days x 12 hours Contract Duration: 13 Weeks Start Date: ASAP About the Position

TravelNurseSource is working with GLC Group, GLC On-The-Go to find a qualified IMC RN in Lake Havasu City, Arizona, 86403!

Position Details
• Specialty: ICU / IMC Float
• Shift Options: 7a-7p or 7p-7a
• Guaranteed Hours: 36/week
• Weekends: Rotating
• Certs Required: ACLS
• Preferred: TNCC, PALS
• Experience Needed:
• 2 years ICU
• 1 year travel
• Float Between:
• ICU Main
• ICU Overflow
• IMC Stepdown Unit Info
• ICU Beds: 16
• IMC Beds: 30 (incl. overflow)
• Ratios:
• ICU 1:2
• IMC 1:3-4
• Population: Adult / Geriatric

About GLC Group, GLC On-The-Go

Recognized as Best Travel Nurse Agency 2024 & 2025 and a three-time Best of Staffing Employee Satisfaction winner, GLC connects Nurses and Allied Health Professionals with opportunities that support real career goals.

Explore Travel, Local, PRN, School-Based, and Government roles nationwide—all backed by a team that values communication, transparency, and readiness.

We focus on reducing delays, keeping you prepared, and making each transition smoother from one assignment to the next.

Whether you’re starting your travel journey or taking your next step, we’re here to support you.

GLC Group proudly operates as an Equal Opportunity Employer. Requirements
• Certs Required: ACLS
• Preferred: TNCC, PALS
• Experience Needed:
• 2 years ICU
• 1 year travel Skills & Equipment
• Required: ICU/Critical Care experience
• Preferred: Mixed ICU, Cardiac, CVICU
• Common Cases: CABG, TAVR, STEMI/NSTEMI, Stroke, Trauma, Cardiovascular, Neuro, Med-Surg ICU/IMC
• Equipment: Baxter pumps, GE monitoring
• EHR: Medhost Benefits
• Weekly on-time pay with direct deposit
• Transparent communication, clear assignment details, and recruiter support from start to finish - or exte]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Primary Care]]></title>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
    <url>https://urbanretreat22-ctrl.github.io/tfa-jobs/jobs/registered-nurse-primary-care-paradise-valley-87.html</url>
    <apply_url>https://tally.so/r/MeOLaX?job_id=87&amp;role=Registered+Nurse+-+Primary+Care&amp;company=Conifer+Health+Solutions</apply_url>
    <company><![CDATA[Conifer Health Solutions]]></company>
    <city>Paradise Valley</city>
    <state>Arizona</state>
    <country>US</country>
    <description><![CDATA[Description

The Registered Nurse is responsible for patient triage and education, assisting physicians during office hours and follow-up on prescriptions, procedures and tests. Maintain chart documentation to ensure all information about visit is completed and documented correctly.

Responsibilities
• Adheres to the mission, purpose, philosophy, policies, and procedures of Tenet Physician Resources.
• Maintains compliance with the Tenet HIPAA Compliance Plan, Privacy Standards, and Corporate Code of Conduct.
• Assists in assessing patient needs by recording vital signs, history, medications, and chief complaints for physician review.
• Performs diagnostic tests and prepares equipment for medical treatments, exams, and procedures as directed.
• Collects and prepares lab specimens for transport, including completion of necessary forms and computer entry.
• Administers prescribed oral medications and provides intramuscular and subcutaneous injections.
• Triages patients to identify emergencies, providing immediate support and notifying providers of urgent medical needs.
• Facilitates patient education, teaching, and the development of care protocols and instructional materials.
• Compiles and analyzes medical and operational data to prepare reports for outcomes and program efficacy.
• Ensures accurate data entry into Electronic Health Records and reviews treatment forms to maximize reimbursement.

Qualifications

Education: High school diploma/GED and completion of an accredited nursing program

 

Certification: Current State RN nursing license. Current CPR certification.

 

Experience: Must have a minimum of two years of clinical experience working in a physician office

#LI-KK1]]></description>
    <salary></salary>
    <jobtype>full-time</jobtype>
    <category>Registered Nurse</category>
  </job>
</source>
